{HEADER:AQAHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEYAAAAA/P/1//T/uv8Auf//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/Or8qsA8avwq++r7qsA7avsq+ur6qsA6avoq+er5qsD5fug/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:27}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:10}
I feel so downhearted that my chest hurts.#

{BLOCK:1}
Who is really to blame for this?@
What exactly drove Tsukishima crazy?#

{BLOCK:2}
Tsukishima shudders like a scared puppy.@
As his soul is now, I could smash it into pieces with only a slight stroke.@
But... would doing that really save anybody?#

{BLOCK:3}
It's true that he commited serious crimes that he must pay for.@
He raped Ruriko (his real little sister), wrecked Ohta's mind, and abused Mizuho, Shinjo (who had nothing to do with this) and the other girls from the student council.@
However, I can't bring myself to hate him.#

{BLOCK:4}
A small, irrelevant piece in the mechanism of his psyche fell off, which affected another cogwheel, and another one, and so on and so forth until eventually altered the spin of a major gear.@
By the time all the gears were malfunctioning, nobody could tell which piece was the first one to fail.#

{BLOCK:5}
Tsukishima is only another victim.@
A sufferer, just like Ruriko.@
He spent all this time agonizing completely alone in this gelid realm of darkness.@
Hurting Ruriko cornered him to this place.#

{BLOCK:6}
Ruriko doesn't hold any grudge against Tsukishima.@
On the contrary, she wanted someone to help him.@
She felt pity for him, she felt sad about him...@ and she was crying for him.@
"Please save him", she cried restlessly as she looked for someone to rescue Tsukishima.#

{BLOCK:7}
As for me, I want to save Ruriko from her grief.#

{BLOCK:8}
That's what I care about the most.@
I hold out my hand to Tsukishima.@
He stares at it with a blank face, blinking repeatedly with his eyes filled with tears.#

{BLOCK:9}
"Let's walk together."@
I move my hand close to Tsukishima.@
At first he was hesitating, but upon seeing a gentle smile on my face, he lowers his guard a bit and timidly grabs my hand.#

{BLOCK:10}
Tsukishima's little hand holds mine.@
I pull it back slowly and make him stand up.@
"Ruriko has forgiven you long time ago."@
"R-Rea... lly?"@
Little Tsukishima repeats a bit shakingly.@
I nod.@
"You simply closed your heart one-sidedly and didn't hear her."@
I pull Tsukishima by the hand and get him out of bed.#

{BLOCK:11}
"Then why doesn't Ruriko come here?@ Why did she leave me alone?!"@
Little Tsukishima points her teary eyes to me and complains with a painful voice.@
"Ruriko hates me!@ That's why she never comes here..."@
"Stop making her suffer!"@
I shout unintentionally.@
Little Tsukishima steps back in fear, which makes me come to my senses and regain composure again.#

{BLOCK:12}
"Tsukishima...@ This is all your fault.@ Do you have the faintest idea how much pain your weak heart has brought to Ruriko?"@
"Then...@ What should I do?@ I...@ I'm sick of being alone.@ I'm happier with Ruriko by my side."@
Tsukishima says with a fragile, sobbing voice.#

{BLOCK:13}
"If that's the case...@ Come out with me.@ You can't pull back Ruriko to this cold and dark abyss.@ If you want to be with her, do it in a warm place under the sun."@
I say calmly.@
It's frustrating, but as I am now, I can't save Ruriko's heart.@.
She...@ needs Tsukishima.@
And Tsukishima needs her too...#

{BLOCK:14}
"Am I making Ruriko suffer now?"@
I nod.@
"If you don't want to see her hurting anymore, come with me.@ Ruriko's waiting for you."#

{BLOCK:15}
"Okay...@ You got it."@
Little Tsukishima wipes his tears and shows me a smile.#

{BLOCK:16}
My electromagnetic waves touched Tsukishima's naked heart and freed it from the pain he felt inside.@
According to the image projected in his heart, I pulled him by the hand and took him out, but actually, he overcame his trauma by himself.@
After all, the human mind is as fragile as glassware; something you can easily break with just a slight hit.@ In order to heal him without hurting him, there's no better bet than letting him open his heart by himself.@
I just gave him the chance to do it.\c
{BG:140600}
\e

{BLOCK:17}
After coming back from Tsukishima's mind, I feel a faint warmth between my arms.@
Realizing it's Ruriko's body warmth, a sense of relief washes over me, as if I came back to a long-missed hometown.@
I open quietly my eyelids.@
I'm inside the gloomy student council room.@
It seems I was embracing Ruriko by the shoulders this whole time during my mental projection.#

{BLOCK:18}
I take a look around the room.@
Due to the influence of our super clash of electromagnetic waves, Mizuho and Shinjo are both knocked out cold.@
On the other hand, Ohta and her friends are asleep since I ordered them to rest with my waves.@
The room is quiet and silent.\c
{VISUAL:051010}
\e

{BLOCK:19}
In front of me is...@ Tsukishima.@
He's sitting on the floor, resting tiredly his upper body against the wall.@
His eyes slightly opened have lost all life in them, dull like those of a dead fish.#
{VISUAL:060707}
\e

{BLOCK:20}
However, little by little, his pupils are now recovering their color.@
Tsukishima blinks repeatedly a couple of times, and his gaze fixes slowly on Ruriko.@
"Ruriko..."@
Tsukishima whispers.@
"I..."#

{BLOCK:21}
"Ruriko..."@
{CHABG:r01141010}
I embrace Ruriko's slim shoulders and tenderly stroke her silky hair and her cheeks.@
She stares at me with a troubled expression on her face.@
"Go ahead."@
I say gently.#

{BLOCK:22}
Actually, I'd have liked to keep embracing Ruriko forever.@
To be honest, I don't want to give her to Tsukishima.@
Even though he's a victim, he's not exempt of all the sins he has comitted.@
However, he's Ruriko's only, irreplaceable brother.@
He can do something I could never be able to do.@
Heal Ruriko's heart...@
I feel a little jealous of him.#

{BLOCK:23}
Ruriko nods silently, leaves my arms, and walks towards Tsukishima.@
{CHARA:r99}
Her eyes fix on Tsukishima, completely immobile.@
"Ruriko...@ I'm sorry...@ I...@ I..."@
Tears spill from Tsukishima's eyes; teardrops that slide quietly along his cheeks and fall to the floor.#

{BLOCK:24}
"You're finally back, big brother..."@
Ruriko whispers in a low voice.@
She sheds pearly teardrops as she looks at Tsukishima.@
Under the smooth moonlight, they both approach each other.\c
{VISUAL:040606}
\e

{BLOCK:25}
This is it, right?@
Ruriko, I...@ fulfilled my promise.#

{BLOCK:26}
I look at both of them feeling indescribably sorrowful.\c
{BGMNEXT:02}
{BGMFOUT}
{BG:010001}
\e