{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABYAAAAA/P/1//T/6v8A6f//q/+r/qsD/ftc/v8AAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
{CHABG:r00311005}
Denpa waves.@
The very moment Tsukishima mentions that word, Ruriko's voice echoes in a corner of my mind.#

{BLOCK:1}
"You can receive denpa waves, can't you, Nagase?"#

{BLOCK:2}
Denpa waves...@
I never imagined I'd hear now that term Ruriko told me about this noon.@
No, if I think about it, perhaps it's only natural.@
Tsukishima and Ruriko are siblings, so it's not strange they share the same oddities.\c
{CHABG:c41140510}
\e