{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAB0AAAAA/P/1//T/4/8A4v//q/+r/qsA/cK//vz7ev4H+3v+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMWAIT}
After a while, Saori finally recovers her mobility.@
First she was numbed by the electric shock, and then she became wildly aroused all of a sudden.@ Up until just a moments ago, she was clearly out of her mind.@
It seems she's still unware of the cause behind it.@

{BLOCK:1}
It's possible that that odd electric current had some effect on her psyche.@
If that's the case, what in the world is actually that current...?#

{BLOCK:2}
Now that I remember, Tsukishima mentioned those denpa waves too.@
Denpa waves... huh?\c
{BGMPLAY:01}
\e