{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABYAAAAA/P/1//T/6v8A6f//q/+r/qsD/ftk/v8AAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
"I-I think they're actually average."@
{CHARA:c2B}
"But, you just..."@
Mizuho looks at me with a furious-red face.@
"We can talk about big and small precisely because it exists a mid-point to compare them.@ Yours are a bit on the small end of the spectrum, but they fit easily into the "average" range."@
I keep the conversation going with that hare-brained theory.\c
{CHARA:c24}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"M-My friends use to say I'm childish, even about my height..."@
Mizuho begins to talk in a low voice.@
"Well, it's true that you're growing at a slower pace than everyone, but you're not SO flat-chested that your breasts are unnoticeable when you touch them..."@
{CHARA:c28}
I say, and she drops her gaze again.@
Perhaps she's really THIS self-conscious about this topic.#

{BLOCK:2}
"N-No, perhaps "unnoticeable" isn't the right word...@ I mean, you have still the soft breasts of a young girl..."@
W-What the hell am I even saying?!@
"......"@
Mizuho's cheeks become even more red.@
Awkwardly, I throw the following quick follow-up:@
"B-Besides, I think they'll grow bigger over time."@
The more I say, the weirder the conversation gets...#