{HEADER:AQAJAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAOIAAAAA/P/1//T/Hv8AHf//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/f4uP4A//rx/PD87/8A7vy3/v7X+u0C/Oz/6/zqjP7pAfzo/Of85v9+/gDB/vzyq+Wr9QCr9Kvzq/L7lhf+q+Q+/+Pg/sD9oPz0gPtg+kD5KvjiZ/j/AAAAAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:30}

{BLOCK:0}
Since I'm going to take her along in this survey, I can't hide it to her anymore.@
I choose to tell her everything sequentially.#

{BLOCK:1}
Three days ago during afternoon lessons, a girl from my class suffered a sudden psychotic attack.@
She left a meaningful diary behind some days prior to said episode.@
From the contents of that journal, several causes for her fit were surmised.@
Alcohol, drugs, and... sex.#

{BLOCK:2}
Shinjo listens to my story in all seriousness.@
In a monotonous tone of voice, I tell her what I experienced, what I heard from I uncle, and every bit of information I've acquired up until now.#

{BLOCK:3}
"I see.@ So that's what you've been investigating, huh?@ Interesting...@ So, since I just happened to spot those suspicious shadows, you asked me about it..."@
"Yes, you've been of great help."@
Apparently convinced, Shinjo crosses her arms and nods to herself.@
"I knew the vice president had a breakdown and then was carried out in an ambulance, but I had no idea they suspected she was doing THAT sort of things...@ I thought she suffered from academic burnout or something along those lines."#

{BLOCK:4}
"At this point we're still not sure about anything.@ Just as you said, the true cause might as well be stress."@
"So they haven't pinpointed the trigger yet, huh?@ Got it.@ Unearthing that is also part of our job, isn't it?"@
She's very eager about this.@
"Since it's come to this, I'm going to take you along."@
However, now that I think about it, we're diving into a REAL mess.@
Shinjo looks like she's having fun, though...@
I let out a deep sigh.\c
{CHARA:r19}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
"If that theory is true, it's freakin' unforgivable!@ I don't know the guy, but how come he had... s-sex with the girl until driving her crazy?@ The poor vice president!"@
Blushing, Shinjo shouts facing the sun so as to hide her embarrassment.@
"That's it!@ I'm gonna find 'em and scold 'em and make them apologize for the ghost fuss!"#

{BLOCK:6}
She's jumping to conclusions again.@
She has quite an aggresive personality.@
{CHARA:r18}
"Nagase!"@
"Uh, yeah?"@
"I bet you've a lot to deal with, but now that I'm by your side, rest assured!@"@
"Good to hear..."@
And she's quite a mood maker, to boot.#

{BLOCK:7}
"Alright!@ Let's kick off the survey this very night!@ I'm out of the club at around 8 P.M, so we'll meet here at 8:30!"@
"Okay."@
SHE's bossing ME around now.@ Great.#

{BLOCK:8}
"Oops, I almost forgot!@ Not sure if you can but, could you, like, drop by a store and grab some burgers or buns?@ I'll be dead hungry by the time I leave.@ All on me, of course."@
"Sure, no problem."#

{BLOCK:9}
"Cool!@ We're golden, then!@ Now, let's check out the hour one last time."@
"H-Half past eight."@
"Where?"@
"Right here."@
"And you'll bring...?"@
"Supper."@
"Rad!@ Don't forget the drinks, too!"@
Shinjo snaps her fingers.#

{BLOCK:10}
"Ok, that'll be all."@
"Huh?@ O-Okay."@
"See you later."@
{CHARA:r99}
Shinjo flashes a wink, turns around and returns to the gym walking leisurely.#

{BLOCK:11}
I feel like I've been left behind.@
I wanted to ask her more in depth about her motives to join the survey so enthusiastically, but she never gave me room to do so.@
No, actually, I think I know the reason why.@
It's true that she finds the ghost fuss intolerable, but more than that, she likes this detective stuff way too much.#

{BLOCK:12}
Good grief...@
This is just like...@
"A mysterious school tour in the dead of the night!@ Look for the criminal!"
that kinda show.@
I'm not sure if taking her along was the right call.@
I know she's the only witness of the nightly meetings, but perhaps I was too careless in recruiting her.#

{BLOCK:13}
I feel somewhat anxious.#

{BLOCK:14}
"Cool!@ We're golden, then!@ Now, let's check out the hour one last time."\n\e

{BLOCK:15}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. "7:30?"\n\e

{BLOCK:16}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. "H-Half past eight."\n\e

{BLOCK:17}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
3. 9 o'clock?\n\e

{BLOCK:18}
"Where?"\n\e

{BLOCK:19}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. "Right here."\n\e

{BLOCK:20}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. "There."\n\e

{BLOCK:21}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
3. "The staff room."\n\e

{BLOCK:22}
"And you'll bring...?"@
\e

{BLOCK:23}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. "A camera."\n\e

{BLOCK:24}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. "A volleyball"\n\e

{BLOCK:25}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
3. "Supper."\n\e

{BLOCK:26}
"Rad!@ Don't forget the drinks, too!"@
Shinjo snaps her fingers.#

{BLOCK:27}
"No, that's not it!@ Once again from the start!!"#

{BLOCK:28}
"What time?"\n\e

{BLOCK:29}
"You're doing it on purpose, aren't you?!"@
"Sorry, I was just pulling your leg.@ We're going to meet here at half past eight, and I'll bring dinner with me."#