{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABQAAAAA/P/1//T/7P8A6///q/+r/vsPhP7/AAAAAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:2}

{BLOCK:0}
{CHARA:r99}
We pass along the row of doors and check if they aren't shedding any light.@
However, as a matter of course, no lights are turned on in such a blatant way.@
The doors are tightly closed too, so we can't check for light sources by peeking inside.\c
{CHARA:r10}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"As I said before, we should guide ourselves by the sound."@
I obediently accept Saori's suggestion.#