{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABYAAAAA/P/1//T/6v8A6f//q/+r/qsD/fs9/v8AAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
"You call that... HARD WORK!"\c
{REFCHAR:L68}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"That's lame!@ All it took you to write this scene was an hour and a half in a single night!@ By then, the development room staff was still hard at work.@ Your efforts can hardly be called HARD work!"\c
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
It's just as the dimensional emperor says.@
No matter how much efforts we spent, we hadn't the power to defeat him.@
Which means that what awaited us beyond was...#