{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACUAAAAA/P/1//T/2/8A2v//q/+r/qsA/av8+Pr7/foA//n71/uL/tcH+4r+/wAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:7}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:480202}
We run along the dim hallway, run up the stairs, and rush to the rooftop.@
{CHARA:r14}
"W-Was it really there?"@
Saori repeats the same question again and again.@
"Yeah! I'm sure!"@
I didn't mistake her for something else.@
I'm 100% sure I saw a girl in uniform up there.\c
{BG:180202}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
Finally, we're done climbing those long stairs.@
Before us is a heavy, gray iron door.@
This is the second time I open this door.@
The first one was when I was talking with my uncle, and the second one when I came with Saori now.@
It's unlocked.@
I grab the knob, tilt it diagonally, and then open the door.#

{BLOCK:2}
*Clank*\c
{BG:190707}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
{PCMLOAD:01}
{PCMPLAY:0100}
*Whooosh!*@
{PCMWAIT}
{PCMFOUT}
In the dead of the night, chill wind blows in from the rooftop.@
At the same time, moonlight shines through the gap of the open door.@
"Y-Yuusuke..."@
Saori holds my arm with an anxious face.@
What happened to her?@
Judging by how brave she acted before, I'd have never imagined she'd be SO scared.#

{BLOCK:4}
Now that I remember, her reaction before was a little odd too.@
Perhaps she's actually a chicken at heart?@
In fact, she looks like she'll sink in fear any minute now.#

{BLOCK:5}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. Ask her if she's scared.\n\e

{BLOCK:6}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. "Don't worry.@ I'm here to protect you."\n\e