{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABsAAAAA/P/1//T/5f8A5P//q/+r/qsA/av8uLT++2Ef/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
"Can you show me that music box?"@
{CHARA:c20}
"Yes."@
Mizuho takes out a small woodden box from her pocket and hands it to me.@
{VISUAL:170808}
{BGMFOUT}
The music box, whose size fits just right in my palm, feels way lighter than I thought.@
It's designed so that the music starts to play as soon as you open the cover.@
I open the box gently.\c
{BGMPLAY:23}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
Perhaps it's because the inner springs are almost unwound, but the music box plays a feeble melody until eventually loses all power and stops working.@
"Ah, please wind the horizontal springs."@
"Like this?"@
"Yes, with that lever."@
I wind the springs with a rattling sound.@
After I let go of the lever, the music box starts again, this time playing a sweet melody.\c
{BGMPLAY:22}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
If this music is deeply rooted in her memories, perhaps it can help to produce some sort of response in Ohta.@
Mizuho's wholehearted wish to save her friend lead her to try every possible method to accomplish it.@
I feel that the resonance of this music box is Mizuho's tender heart voice itself.\c
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMNEXT:06}
{CHABG:c20480505}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
"As long as you keep her in your heart, Ohta will someday go back to her usual self.@ That's what I feel."@
I say closing the lid of the box.@
I'm not trying to console her.@ I mean every word I say.@
{CHARA:c2A}
"Y-Yuusuke..."@
Mizuho wipes her tears with the back of her hand.@
"T-Thank you so much..."@
She says smiling.#