{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAB8AAAAA/P/1//T/4f8A4P//q/+r/qsA/av8wrj+/PsB0/770v7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
"I'd like you to tell me if you noticed something strange about Ohta before the incident."@
{CHARA:r24}
"Well..."@
Mizuho averts her gaze from me and drops her head.@
"I never noticed Ohta was becoming insane until that very day.@ I thought she was her usual self."\

{BLOCK:1}
{CHARA:r2A}
Mizuho bites her lower lip.@
"I'm an idiot, aren't I?@ I'm supposed to be her best friend and I couldn't even notice those subtle changes in her..."@
"Mizuho..."@
{CHARA:r24}
"If only I realized it sooner, I would have listened to Kanako's problems and helped her somehow.@ I'm sure she would have never lost her mind that way..."\

{BLOCK:2}
Mizuho keeps hanging her head for a while.@
I have no idea what to answer.@
"I don't care if it's too late.@ I just want to do something for Kanako..."@
Now I realize how much Mizuho cares about Ohta as a friend.@
Perhaps Ohta was a girl worth of such a strong friendship, and perhaps she felt the same way about Mizuho.\

{BLOCK:3}
However, even if only temporarily, their bond has become toxic.@
Despite it's illogical, Mizuho feels guilty about not being able to save her before it was too late.@
Maybe she wants to free herself from her guilt during the few hours she'd be busy trying to help Ohta.\