{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACoAAAAA/P/1//T/1v8A1f//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/P7yf4//wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:13}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
One of my cheeks feels cold, but the other one feels warm.#

{BLOCK:1}
I just noticed I fell asleep.@
However, my drowsiness recedes little by little, and at the same pace, I open my eyelids.#

{BLOCK:2}
A human-like figure appears in my hazy field of vision.@
I wonder who it is...@
I'm lying down on the floor and resting my head on their lap.@
Eventually, my blurred vision comes into focus and I realize the person is actually Ruriko.@
The warmth I felt in one of my cheeks came from her lap, and the coldness I felt in the other came from her hand.@
She peeks into my face fixedly.\c
{BGMPLAY:08}
{VISUAL:011100}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
"Ruriko?"@
"Hello."@
She says in a low voice.@
As if pulled by a thread, I slowly sit upright.@
My head feels heavy, just like if I lifted it forcibly after oversleeping.@
"Where am I?"#

{BLOCK:4}
The sky has gotten completely dark.@
A full, round moon is up, and beyond the fence I can see the lights of the city.@
"It's night..."@
A pretty obvious thing to say.@ I shake slightly my head, but then I feel a sharp twinge of pain in it.#

{BLOCK:5}
Judging by the situation around, it looks like I lost consciousness for a good while.@
Did Ruriko stay by my side all this time?@
I wonder if I had that dream because she was here with me...@
That dream...#

{BLOCK:6}
Ruriko cowering and quivering...@
Her teardrops flowing down her cheeks...@
The light ripples that spread across that puddle...#

{BLOCK:7}
"Ruriko...@ You were crying..."@
My mouth speaks by itself.@
"You were crying...@ all while looking terribly sad."#

{BLOCK:8}
That was a dream.@ I have no doubt that it was just that.@
But...@
"Who made you cry?@ Why were you so sad?"@
I ask her as I stare at her face.#

{BLOCK:9}
It's no use to ask her that, since she has no way to answer.@
In fact, she's now looking at me with a troubled expression.@
Nonetheless, I just can't accept that it was only a dream.@
"Who made you like this, Ruriko?@ Why did you become like this?"@
I touch softly her cheek and stroke her smooth skin with the back of my hand.#

{BLOCK:10}
"Someone hurt you, am I wrong?"@
My field of vision becomes blurry.@
Huh?@ What's going on?@
"What's wrong, Naga?@ Do you feel sad?"@
Ruriko looks at me on the verge of tears.#

{BLOCK:11}
"Don't cry, Naga."@
Me?@ Crying?@ Why?@ You were crying, not me, Ruriko...@
Ruriko pats gently my head.@
This is weird.@ This is not normal.@ I mean, our roles have now reversed...#

{BLOCK:12}
Tears dropped from my eyes.@
Teardrop after teardrop...@
dripping endlessly.\c
{BGMFOUT}
{BG:360000}
\e