{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACMAAAAA/P/1//T/3f8A3P//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+sIAuP78+9P++9If/v8AAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:6}

{BLOCK:0}
"You have already heard that Ohta has been coming to school late by night since three weeks prior to the incident, right?"@
"Yes."@
"You don't know anything about that?@ Y'know, something you heard from her by chance..."@
{CHARA:r24}
Mizuho shakes her head apologetically.\

{BLOCK:1}
"No, she never told me anything about that, but..."@
"But?"@
"Ohta's mom called me once asking me if Kanako didn't come to my house."@
"And that happened...?"@
"About three weeks ago."\

{BLOCK:2}
Naturally, at some point Ohta's mom wondered where the hell her daughter went every night.@
"However, when we had that call, Kanako's mom never mentioned she parted home every night.@ She only asked me if her daughter came here, and I answered with the truth: that she didn't.@ That's all."@
"I see...@ I thought you'd know since you're so close to Ohta."@
"I'm sorry."@
"No need to apologize.@ It's not your fault."\c
{CHARA:r21}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
"No, I'm partially to blame for this."@
"Partially?"@
"Yes.@ Despite I'm her friend, I didn't know anything about the problems she was facing.@ I wasn't able to help her until she became like that."@
"You're just overthinking.@ No matter how intimate you were, you're still different persons.@ There's boundaries you can never cross."\

{BLOCK:4}
Normally, I'm not the kinda guy who says things like these.@
However, right now I want to console Mizuho so badly I'm looking for words I'm not used to say.@
"It's pointless to blame yourself."@
{CHARA:r20}
"Yuusuke..."@
Mizuho wipes her tears and looks at me.@
"T-Thank you."\

{BLOCK:5}
I feel my heart beating slightly faster than normal.\