{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACYAAAAA/P/1//T/2v8A2f//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsD9fvI/v8AAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:11}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
One of my cheeks feels cold, but the other one feels warm.#

{BLOCK:1}
I just noticed I lost consciousness.@
However, I come to my senses little by little, and at the same pace, I open my eyelids.#

{BLOCK:2}
A human-like figure appears in my hazy field of vision.@
I wonder who it is...@
I'm lying down on the floor and resting my head on their lap.@
Eventually, my blurred vision comes into focus and I realize the person is actually Ruriko.@
The warmth I felt in one of my cheeks came from her lap, and the coldness I felt in the other came from her hand.@
She peeks into my face fixedly.\c
{BGMPLAY:08}
{VISUAL:011100}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
"Ruriko?"@
"......"@
She's completely silent.@
As if pulled by a thread, I slowly sit upright.@
My head feels heavy, just like if I lifted it forcibly after oversleeping.@
"Where am I?"#

{BLOCK:4}
The sky has gotten completely dark.@
A full, round moon is up, and beyond the fence I can see the lights of the city.@
"It's night..."@
A pretty obvious thing to say.@ I shake slightly my head, but then I feel a sharp twinge of pain in it.#

{BLOCK:5}
Judging by the situation around, it looks like I lost consciousness for a good while.@
Did Ruriko stay by my side all this time?@
I wonder if I had that dream because she was here with me...#

{BLOCK:6}
Ruriko stares direcltly into my eyes with a somewhat cold expression on her face, but eventually she opens her mouth slowly.@
"You lied to me, Naga."@
A cold voice devoid of all emotion.#

{BLOCK:7}
{CHABG:c01331010}
"You lied about using the denpa waves.@ You still haven't that power."@
For some reason, Ruriko's eyes look sorrowful.@
That makes my chest hurt with guilt.@
"I-I'm sorry.@ I... I just..."@
Awkwardly, I try to keep appereances.@
However, I don't find anything appropriate to say.@
"I-I...@ I just...@ wanted...@ to see the same delusion as you."#

{BLOCK:8}
"Delusion?"@
Ruriko whispers as she slowly stands up.@
Then, she tells me with those sad eyes...@
"You're just like everyone else, Naga.@ You make fun of denpa waves.@ How can you call them a "delusion"?"@
"N-No..."@
"Goodbye."@
Beautiful gem-like teardrops spill from her eyes.@

{BLOCK:9}
She turns around and slowly walks away.@
{CHARA:c99}
"R-Ruriko!"@
I chase her back desperately, but strangely, my body doesn't move an inch.@
It's just like it isn't my own body.@
"Ruriko!"#

{BLOCK:10}
My body stands still against the fence for a while after she takes her leave.\c
{BGMNEXT:03}
{BGMFOUT}
{BG:360505}
\e