{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABYAAAAA/P/1//T/6v8A6f//q/+r/qsD/fvR/v8AAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
Her feelings seems to be genuine.@
She cares about Ohta more than anyone else, so I'm sure she's taking this case more seriously than anybody.\

{BLOCK:1}
That said, just a while before I agreed investigating with Shinjo.@
If the three of us patrol we'll stand out, and our coordination will only get worse.@
And, given her current mental state, I feel Mizuho will be in danger.@
She's tormenting herself about this, after all.\

{BLOCK:2}
I'm sorry for Mizuho, but I'll have to reject her.\