{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABsAAAAA/P/1//T/5f8A5P//q/+r/sIAv//8+9n++9gf/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:2}

{BLOCK:0}
Yeah, the most important piece of information is that the ghost craze started two or three weeks ago.@
If we assume the ghost fuss was originated after the participants of the orgy were spotted as my uncle mentioned, that matches almost perfectly with the contents in Ohta's diary.\

{BLOCK:1}
That further reinforces the theory that fishy meetings are happening at school at night.\