{HEADER:AQAIAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAFYAAAAA/P/1//T/qv8Aqf//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/Or8qsA8avwq++r7qsA7avsq+ur6qsA6avoq+er5qsA5avkq+Or4qsA4avgq9+r3qsD3fut/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:35}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:19}
"R-Ruriko...@ Get away...@ from me..."@
I desperately fight back my desire.@
Ruriko pushes her cheek against my chest and stares up at me.@
Whenever she breathes, the tender mounds of her chest press onto mine.@
I grab her shoulders and forcefully draw her away, but as soon as I place my hands on them, the fear of losing my last bit of self-restraint assaults me.#

{BLOCK:1}
"Ru...@ ri...@ ko...@ Hu...@ rry...@ up..."@
I can't afford to lose...@ I won't give in to Tsukishima's waves...@
"Are you suffering, Naga?"@
Concerned, Ruriko looks into my face.@
Her soft breasts press even harder against my body,@
and my reason is about to succumb to my lust.@
"You look like...@ you're in pain."@
Her gentle voice surrounds me.#

{BLOCK:2}
Cracks develop in my glass-fragile sanity.@
Soon, my rampaging thirst will break it and take control over me.@
And then...@ I'll end up raping Ruriko.@
Not because I'm being controlled by Tsukishima, but by my own will.@
He said toxic waves cause human brains to malfunction and let loose their repressed desires.@
That desire of raping her, of defiling her...@ is my own craving lurking inside me.#

{BLOCK:3}
My skin gets covered in sweat,@
and a voice inside screams "do it".@
"She isn't so bad of a prey", says the nauseating voice.@
However, this temptation feels comfortable, and sweetly sensual.@
Her cherry colored lips...@ Her white, fair skin...@ Her mushy bosom...@
I want to rape her, desecrate her, copulate with her...@
I'm at my limit.@
I can't hold back my desire anymore.#

{BLOCK:4}
"Naga..."@
Her sweet breath tickles my nape, and I feel the texture of her breasts through my uniform.@
Ruriko,@ Ruriko,@ Ruriko,@ Ruriko,@ Ruriko!@
With a loud blast, my rationality breaks in pieces.@
"I'm sorry, Ruriko."@
Both of my arms detach from my consciousness and embrace Ruriko's slender back.@
"I-I can't resist it a second longer..."#

{BLOCK:5}
Then, her kind voice reaches my ears.@
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
"I'll save you, Naga."@
Her voice sounds like she's speaking directly to my mind.@
{BGMPLAY:12}
"I swear I will."@
"Save... me...?"@
"I promised, remember?"@
"You... promised...?"@
As my field of vision becomes gradually hazy, a certain scene flashes through my mind.\c
{VISUAL:010505}
\e

{BLOCK:6}
Alone under the smooth moonlight of a yellow, large full moon, we embraced each other on the rooftop.@
As she stroked my back with her cold hands, she said:@
"I'll save you.@ I promise I'm gonna save you, Naga, so please don't cry anymore, okay?"@
Ruriko kept staring at my face with those unfocused eyes akin to a nocturnal lake.\c
{VISUAL:210505}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
"I'll save you from your suffering...@ From my brother's waves...@ From your loneliness...@ I swear..."@
From Tsukishima's waves?!@
"R-Ruriko...@ You..."@
My ears don't lie.@ She said "my brother's waves" just now.@
"I see...@ Yeah, of course..."@
Upon hearing her words, everything becomes clear to me.@
"Ruriko...@ You always knew about all this, didn't you?"#

{BLOCK:8}
Ruriko smiles compassionately and presses her delicate lips against mine.@
"!"@
After that brief contact, Ruriko slowly draws apart her lips, and then, she whispers in a sleepy voice:@
"Do what you wish with me, Naga..."@
She already noticed my desire dwelling inside my heart.@
She's aware of it, and yet she's trusting her body...@
"I love...@ you..."@
and her heart to me...#

{BLOCK:9}
"Ruriko..."@
I surrender myself to the primal urges flaring up inside me, and embrace her dainty, brittle body as strongly as I can.@
Little by little, my sinister hunger disappears from my soul.@ In turn, a pretty warm feeling of satisfaction wells up in it.@
My sadistic desire to rape her turns into a wholesome wish to become one with her.@
Ruriko lives inside me now, and I'm madly in love with her.#
{BG:260707}
\e

{BLOCK:10}
We move to the gym's storage room in front of us.@
This gloomy room is packed with mold-smelling air inside, but for us, that have only eyes for each other, that couldn't be less important.@
{HSCENE:261010}
*Poof*@ I lay Ruriko on the dusty exercise mat.@
The yellow moonlight coming from the window makes the scattered dust floating in the air sparkle.@
After inhaling a good lungful of that dust, we exchange a passionate kiss.#

{BLOCK:11}
I take my time to unfasten the scarf of Ruriko's uniform with my shaking fingertips.@
Her scarf, supposed to be red, looks dark brown under the moonlight.@ *Fwip*@ I slide it off her nape and it falls fluttering to the floor, right next to us.@
Ruriko wears a docile expression on her face as she looks at me with anxiety.@
My heart is beating really fast.#

{BLOCK:12}
"R-Ruriko...@ I-I love you..."@
This is my very first love confession to her.@
She narrows her eyes and answers me with a comfortable smile.#

{BLOCK:13}
I reach out my fingertips towards her chest and touch one the round buttons in her uniform.@ Then, I unfasten the three buttons on it, one at a time, and open the chest part up.@
{HSCENE:279912}
The cool air of the storage room grazes Ruriko's pale skin.@
For a brief moment, her body shivers.#

{BLOCK:14}
My line of sight is fixed on Ruriko's pure white bra, which I touch gingerly with my trembling palm.@
It feels elastic and warm; its modest size fits just right in the center of my hand.@
I apply pressure carefully on Ruriko's chest with my palm.@
"Ah...", she mumbles.#

{BLOCK:15}
"S-Sorry, did it hurt?"@
I hear my heart throbbing intensely.@
Ruriko slowly shakes her head.@
"No...@ It feels...@ good..."@
Her voice sounds sweet and painful at a time.@
*Thump*@ *Thump*@ My crotch is throbbing fiercely.@
*Fwip*@ I grab the edge of Ruriko's white bra and slide it up.@
This will sound pathetic, but I have no idea how to unfasten it.#

{BLOCK:16}
Ruriko's porcelain breasts are now exposed.@
Her snowy skin bathed in the faint moonlight looks extremely erotic.@
Crowning her silken, velvety hills are her nipples, akin to cherry-colored buds.@
I bring my lips close to them and plant a kiss on them.@
When I first hold them with my lips they feel soft to the touch, but as I lick them with the tip of my tongue, they eventually harden up inside my mouth.@
They become erected when stimulated.@ I can understand that, of course, since I'm a male.#

{BLOCK:17}
I eagle grip Ruriko's fleshy nipples with my right hand and rub them ever so gently, being careful not to apply too much force.@
This time I realize Ruriko's nipples have become fully erect by feeling them in the center of my palm.@
I keep massaging her breasts and sucking her nipples for a while, absent-mindedly.@
"Nh!@ Nh!"@ From time to time she lets out painful moans, but nonetheless, she strokes gently my hair with her hands.@
Surrounded by an odd sense of relief similar to being embraced by a mother, my nervousness fades away gradually from my quivering body.#

{BLOCK:18}
I put my hand in the waist area of her skirt, unfasten the lateral hook and unzip it.@
I'm more or less familiar with the structure of skirts.@
I remove hers sliding it down her thighs.@
Facing slightly downwards, Ruriko peeks into my eyes shyly as her skirt falls to her feet.@
Wearing nothing but her underwear, and with the coat of her uniform off, I embrace Ruriko tight.#

{BLOCK:19}
Holding her in my arms, I stroke her satiny abdomen.@
And then, catching her on the hop, I slide some fingers inside her panties.@
"Ah!", she moans.@
I apply pressure on her pubic mound using the balls of my fingers.@
After making sure her body reacts with a twitch, I join two fingertips and slide them up and down sluggishly on her slightly wet crevice.#

{BLOCK:20}
"Ah...@ Aaah...@ Ah...!"@
Ruriko gasps painfully.@
I push aside the hot nectar dripping from her vagina using my fingertips and keep fiddling with it.@
"Nff..."@ She gives out sweet, twangy moans as her body jerks in response to my caresses.#

{BLOCK:21}
I lay my hand on her panties, slightly drenched with love juices, and smoothly glide them down her thighs.@
{HSCENE:289912}
I lift her legs up and slide her panties from her thighs to her knees and then all the way down to her ankles.@ By the moment I remove them off her feet, they take the form of a small ball.#

{BLOCK:22}
With the indecent appearance of only the coat of her uniform and her socks covering her body, she stares at me with a helpless expression.@
I place a hand on her sleek thighs and slowly open up her legs, revealing her shy, beautiful, pink colored sexual organ.@
The nectar leaking from her intimate zone shines under the moonlight.@
Perhaps embarrassed, Ruriko covers her mouth with her hands with a face on the verge of tears.\c
{HSCENE:291010}
\e

{BLOCK:23}
"Ruriko...@ You're beautiful..."@
I whisper subduedly before bringing my lips close to her cute sexual organ, and then let my tongue run across it.@
"Ah...@ Ah...@ Aaah!"@
*Twitch!*@ Her lower half jerks.@
*Schlup*@ *Schlup*@ Making my tongue job deliberately loud, I continue to lick Ruriko's intimate zone.@
Her love juices taste slightly bitter.@
My saliva mixes with her sexual fluids.@
I slide my tongue up and down along her crack, placing special emphasis around the area of her vaginal opening.#

{BLOCK:24}
I curl up my tongue and stick the tip out in order to thrust it into her vagina.@
Ruriko's body twitches with convulsions.@
She's so cute...@ That's what I think from the bottom of my heart.@
As my tongue makes wet sounds, I move it a bit upwards.@
After giving two, three licks to her urethral opening, I go above it and reach her clit, a cute bud enveloped in a hood that I fondle with my tongue.@
In that very instant, Ruriko's body jerks intensely like it never did before.#

{BLOCK:25}
"Fuaah...@ Fuaaaah!"@
Giving out agonizing moans, Ruriko points her teary eyes to me.@
While I caress her with the tip of my tongue repeatedly, her tiny clitoris becomes gradually harder until it eventually pops out shyly from its foreskin.@
Having her most sensitive zone of her body attacked by my tongue, Ruriko lets out small, concealed, but agonizing gasps.@
I mercilessly make my tongue crawl all over her vagina.#

{BLOCK:26}
"Ah, aaah, Naga..."@
Ruriko keeps delivering sweet, sensual moans.@
After confirming Ruriko's vagina is enough moistened with nectar, I put a stop to the strokes of my tongue and wipe my mouth.@
I bring my face right in front of her eyes, and she stares at me awkwardly with weeping eyes.#

{BLOCK:27}
"I want to... enter inside you, Ruriko."@
I tell her how I feel now honestly.@
"I want to become one with you, to have sex with you."@
Embarrassed, Ruriko gazes intently at me, and then nods quietly.@
"Ruriko..."@
I kiss her hard.@
Wet with her love juices, I tangle my tongue with hers.#

{BLOCK:28}
I unzip my pants and take my boiling hot penis out of them.@
Ruriko's cute naked body and actions stimulate me thoroughly and make me hard like never before.@
I can't wait anymore.@
I want to have intercourse with her right now.@
I want to feel her insides with this sensitive part of mine.@
I want to enter inside her.\c
{HSCENE:301010}
\e

{BLOCK:29}
I place the tip of my cock by her vagina.@
*SFX*@ I push in my hips.@
However, after two or three attempts, I can't insert it well.@
Despite I caressed her so up-close, and that I know the color and form of her vagina, I'm unable to pinpoint the correct position now that I've placed my lower half with hers.@
Embarrassed, I start to feel impatient.#

{BLOCK:30}
As I enter in a panic, Ruriko grabs gently, softly my rod with her cold palm.@
"R-Ruri..."@
I look at Ruriko, and she stares down at the mat covering her face in shame.@
She slowly guides my shaft with her hand.@
Soon after, my tip sinks into her opening with a small sound.#

{BLOCK:31}
"T-Thank you..."@
Well, maybe I shouldn't have said thanks.@
Ruriko frowns, and looks up at me blushing shyly.@
"H-Here I go, Ruriko."@
I slowly lower my hips.#

{BLOCK:32}
*Zum*@ *Zum*@ Little by little, my pole sinks into her vagina.@
"Nh...@ Nnnh!"@
Ruriko shakes her head and lets out a cute nasal moan.\c
{HSCENE:311010}
\e

{BLOCK:33}
Eventually, my penis gets buried deep into her vagina all the way to the base.@
My tip touches her deepest spot.@
Ruriko's insides are scorching hot, and very pleasant.@
*Clutch*@ Her soft vaginal walls tighten around my tool.#

{BLOCK:34}
Covered in slimy love juices, our sexual organs connect without space between them.@
"Haaaaa..."@
Ruriko lets out a painful breath and clings to me.@
I slowly move my hips.@
Despite her vagina is plenty wet, and even overflowing with lube, it constricts my rod and doesn't let me go.@
Even if I pull out little by little, I feel like I'm gonna finish right off the bat.#