{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACgAAAAA/P/1//T/2P8A1///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0+7j+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:12}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
Where did Mizuho go?@
It must be a place relatively close to the emergency exit...#

{BLOCK:1}
{FLASH}
Right then, along with the scratchy touch of electric current, the name of a certain room pops up in a corner of my mind.@
The student council.@
Of course...@
That room is literally around the corner.@
It's very likely that Mizuho headed there, since she's a member of the S.C.\c
{BG:000011}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
I lead Ruriko by the hand, and we go around the backdoor of the school building.@
There's a parking lot for bikes there.@
There's a narrow gap between buildings there, and if we go through that small opening, we can get out to a courtyard surrounded by the buildings.@
That breach barely allows a single person to pass through, but in the middle there's a window to the student council's room.@
We cross that slender crack, and move in front of the window.\c
{BG:161103}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
The window is covered with a black curtain, and I can't even tell if the fluorescent lamps are on inside.@
Worse even, the windows frame is firmly enveloped in aluminium sash, thus not allowing any sound to leak.@
I put my ear against the window and listen attentively.#

{BLOCK:4}
"!"@
{BGMPLAY:09}
Though faintly, I hear people conversating inside.@
I don't know what they're talking about behind this glass window, but it sounds like girls' voices.@
I think I heard Mizuho's voice...@
and the voice of another girl, too.@
The voices sound strange, as if they're not holding a conversation at all.@ Like animal groans, but "feminine".@
Are those girls... gasping?#

{BLOCK:5}
Whatever the case may be, it's almost certain that people is inside the room.@ Two girls, at least.@
Unfortunately, I have no idea what they're doing.@
Nonetheless, I hear Mizuho's voice (which I'm assuming is hers) screaming.#

{BLOCK:6}
At that moment, I hear a male voice mixed with the girls' ones.@
Are there three of them?@
I thought so at first, but now I hear an anguish cry along with the laugh of the man.@
I hear gasps, too.@
He's not alone.@
There's at least two persons inside.#

{BLOCK:7}
What the hell are they doing in there?@
I'm not sure how accurate was my uncle's theory, but it seems he wasn't too off the mark.@
Mizuho must be witnessing unspeakable horrors inside.#

{BLOCK:8}
This is no good.@
I'm not getting anywhere staying here.@
When I separate my ear from the glass window, I feel the window slides slightly.@
No way...!@
I touch the window carefully and apply force in my fingertips.@
Then, the window slides smoothly to one side.@
It isn't locked!#

{BLOCK:9}
I don't know if it's just a coincidence or it's open on purpose, but either way, I'm lucky.@
Taking care that the curtains doesn't get swayed by the wind, I quietly open the window without making any sound.#

{BLOCK:10}
At that instant, as if suddenly turning the volume of a TV, I hear the voices from inside loud and clear.@
"Stop, Kanako!"@
As I thought, it was Mizuho.@
That was, undoubtedly, her voice.@
She's definitely inside there.#

{BLOCK:11}
Mizuho just screamed "Kanako".@
Kanako...?@
Does she mean THAT Kanako Ohta?@
Is she inside that room now?!@
I softly open the black curtain with a finger to peek inside.@
And there...#