{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACUAAAAA/P/1//T/2/8A2v//q/+r/qsA/av8/v77q/oAq/mr+Kv3q/YH+8r+/wAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:10}

{BLOCK:0}
"Yeah, your denpa waves reached my head.@ They led me here."@
I play along with her prank.@
"Really?"@
Ruriko looks at me doubtfully.@
"Y-Yeah, it's true.@ I received your waves loud and clear."@
I keep going, though perhaps I'm taking this a bit too far.#

{BLOCK:1}
"I don't know if it's some kind of telepathic power, but I heard your voice.@ I came here because I thought I HAD to meet you."@
I'm aware I'm just speaking carelessly.@
Actually, I didn't feel those "denpa waves" at all.@
I just wanted to talk with Ruriko about this strange topic.@
I felt I could get closer to her that way.#

{BLOCK:2}
"So you can use denpa waves now, right, Naga?"@
Ruriko says tilting her head.@
"Uh...@ Y-Yeah."@
"I KNEW we were alike."@
"S-Sure we are..."@
I just wanted to pull her leg, but seeing her sincere smile makes me feel guilty.#

{BLOCK:3}
"If that's the case, feel this..."@
She whispers as she approaches a step closer.@
Her silky hair flutters in the wind.@
"Huh?"@
"My denpa waves are not verbal, but visual."@
Ruriko narrows her eyes.@
"H-Hold on, R-Ruriko..."\c
{BGMNEXT:01}
{BGMFOUT}
{BG:351010}
\e

{BLOCK:4}
At that moment, I feel the world bends as easily as if made of rubber.@

{BLOCK:5}
{VISUAL:021100}
All of a sudden, my heart starts pounding as heavily as an alarm bell, and blood runs through my body with the force of a broken dam.@
"W-What's going on?"@
My brain tickles.@ It feels like electricity particles are flowing across it...@
The physical illusion of a million of hot THINGS gathering inside my body makes me break a sweat.@
My body is hot.@ As hot as burning flames.#

{BLOCK:6}
"My denpa waves are traveling inside you, aren't they?"@
Ruriko looks fixedly at me.@
The current running through my brain goes beyond tickling and now stings.@
My whole body is covered in sweat, and I feel like vomiting.@
"W-Wait, Ruriko.@ I..."@
However, she keeps frozen in place, without answering anything.#

{BLOCK:7}
{FLASH}
I feel the amount of current biting my brain suddenly increased.@
I shiver as the area between my eyebrows gets hotter.@
"Rurururu...@ riririri...@ kokokoko..."@
My field of vision starts to shake like a broken 8mm film.@
Forgetting myself, I approach Ruriko and cling to her.#

{BLOCK:8}
I can't believe it.@ Are these Ruriko's denpa waves?@
Something cold wets my cheek.@
Without even realizing it, I find myself crying my eyes away.#

{BLOCK:9}
Eventually, I lose conciousness.\c
{BG:000007}
\e