{HEADER:AQAGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAADgAAAAA/P/1//T/yP8Ax///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/Or8qsA8avwq++r7qsA7avs+8/+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:20}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMNEXT:03}
{BGMFOUT}
{BG:470606}
In order to meet Ruriko, I climb the stairs that lead to the rooftop.@
After walking upstairs through the steel-cold, gray steps, I open the heavy iron door which was already slightly opened.#

{BLOCK:1}
I'm sure she's there.@
She'll welcome me with an empty smile as the bright-red, sepia-colored sun looms behind her, her fine hair streaming in the wind.@
I have no doubt she's there.@
I don't know why, but strangely, I'm absolutely certain of it.\c
{BG:060505}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
After leaving Mizuho behind, I went immediately to Ruriko's classroom to pay her a visit.@
However, she was not there.@
She couldn't possibly have gone home, so she must be somewhere in the school.@
After all, her bag was still on her desk.#

{BLOCK:3}
I asked Ruriko's whereabouts to a student in the classroom.@
"Tsukishima?@ Ah, you mean that crazy bitch?"@
That was the very first thing he said.@
It's evident her classmates are blatantly keeping her at arm's lenght.#

{BLOCK:4}
She was never a chatterbox to begin with, but since last year's fall she stopped talking with everyone almost completely.@
Apparently, a certain day she cut ties with her close friends out of the blue, becoming basically a recluse.@
Whenever they tried to talk with her she took the conversation to denpa waves, signals and that kind of stuff, making it clear that she was not all there.#

{BLOCK:5}
Just like Ohta, rumors started to spread that the cause of her insanity was stress, psychosis, drugs, etc.@
However, since her symptoms were far less serious than Ohta's, she could still attend school normally.@
She spooked everyone around her with her obscure behavior, but nothing more scandalous than that.\c
{BG:470505}
\e

{BLOCK:6}
Ruriko cut all form of communication with the people around her.@
She closed her heart and broke relationships even with her best friends.@
However, she wasn't like that when I met her earlier today.\c
{CHABG:r00310505}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
When we met in the rooftop, she talked with me relaxedly and laughed all the time.@
She didn't give me the impression of a solitary girl at all.@
Back then she seemed like she just wanted to talk with someone for a change.@
No, that's not quite right.@
Why, then?#

{BLOCK:8}
"You're just like me, aren't you, Nagase?"#

{BLOCK:9}
That's what she said.@ She stated that we were alike.@
She said that because I'm indeed similar to her...@ No, I'm not sure about that, but at the very least I can tell the actual reason she opened her heart to me was because she THOUGHT we were on the same wavelenght.@
That's what I feel.@
If that's the case, why does she think about me as a friend?#

{BLOCK:10}
"You can receive denpa waves, can you?"#

{BLOCK:11}
Ruriko was talking about denpa waves' reception.@
To be honest, I don't have that kind of power.@
Not only that: I don't even understand the concept behind the denpa waves she mentioned.@
As far as that matter goes, I can only conclude it's a misunderstanding on her part.#

{BLOCK:12}
Nonetheless, I consider her a friend as well.@
That's because...#

{BLOCK:13}
She opened the door towards the world of insanity.#

{BLOCK:14}
I'm ABOUT to open it too.@
Ohta, on the other hand, opened it BY ACCIDENT.@
What about Ruriko, then?@
How far did she go into that world after opening the door...?\c
{BG:550505}
\e

{BLOCK:15}
As I think about that, I find myself already on the last step of the stairs.@
Before me is the heavy-looking, gray iron door that leads to the rooftop.@
It's unlocked.@
The light of the deep-red sun filters through the small gap between it and the outside.#

{BLOCK:16}
I open the door.@
{BG:351010}
The setting sun spreading through the sky dyes the urban landscape below my gaze with a reddish sepia hue.@
The contrast between the sun and the shadows, and the vibrant crimson sunlight burns my eyes.#

{BLOCK:17}
A black shadow stands in front of the bright-red sun as if melting with it, and I slowly approach it.\c
{BGMNEXT:08}
{BGMFOUT}
{VISUAL:030000}
\e

{BLOCK:18}
Ruriko was always staring fixedly at the door, just as if she knew I'd come to visit her.@
The cold wind sways the thin strands of her hair and the hem of her uniform.#

{BLOCK:19}
Just as I thought,@
she's waiting for me with an empty smile on her face.#