{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABsAAAAA/P/1//T/5f8A5P//q/+r/sIAv//8+9n++9gf/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:2}

{BLOCK:0}
Yeah, the most important bit of info is that the "ghosts" usually appear at 9-10 pm.@
If we assume the ghost fuss was originated after the participants of the orgy were spotted as my uncle mentioned, I can narrow down by a lot the ideal time for the survey.\

{BLOCK:1}
I'll begin the actual investigation at 9 P.M.\