{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABYAAAAA/P/1//T/6v8A6f//q/+r/qsD/fvA/v8AAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:110303}
Based on Shinjo's testimony, we patrol near the 2nd gym.@
The 2nd gym is the newest one and is used by the volleyball club, which is known for being one of the strongest teams in the prefecture.@ They always stay up late practicing.@
That said, there's not a soul left at these hours.#

{BLOCK:1}
The moonlight projects our shadows clearly on the floor, and thanks to that, we can see very far away without any light source.@
Sakura trees line up around the gym.@
For now, we just walk along it.@
We make sure we don't miss any shadow or light source.@ However, in the end, we don't find anything.#

{BLOCK:2}
Next we enter the gym.@
The door is locked.@
I insert the master key my uncle gave me.@
However, the key doesn't work.@
Apparently, this key only works inside the school building which the gym doesn't belong to.@
Our search range narrowed a little, but there's hardly anything we can do about it.@
If the investigation continues until tomorrow, I'll ask for this key to my uncle.#