{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACEAAAAA/P/1//T/3/8A3v//q/+r/qsA/av8q/vCvP4A/PvE/vvF/v9/AAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:5}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:360303}
Ruriko's by my side.@
We stayed together in the rooftop since then, just the two of us.@
It's not like we did anything special.@ We just let time pass quietly without muttering a word and embracing each other.#

{BLOCK:1}
Eventually, it becomes the time to start the investigation.#

{BLOCK:2}
She decides to join the survey as if it were only natural, and curiosly, I accepted it as a matter of fact too.@
I can't deny I rejected Shinjo and Mizuho over preference for Ruriko.@
This investigation is indeed dangerous, and it'll problematic if it becomes too late.@
Also, if Ruriko finds herself in danger, I'm not sure if I'll be able to protect her.#

{BLOCK:3}
That said, I can't stop thinking that she has something to do with this incident.@
It's just a baseless conjecture, but I think she knows something important and she'll tell me when the right time comes.
That's why I decided to take her along.#

{BLOCK:4}
No, actually, there's a reason more important than that...@
Just like I am now, I need her more than anything.@
Her thin hair, her pale skin, her soft chest...@ I want her and everything that defines her to be by my side.@
To say all the truth, those feelings weight more in my decision than anything.#