{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAB0AAAAA/P/1//T/4/8A4v//q/+r/qsA/cK///z72f4H+9j+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
` Judging by Shinjo's story, it seems we're dealing with a group of at least three girls.@ They could be more, though.@
` Keeping in mind I might run into them by accident, it's obviously beneficial to have a previous grasp of their numbers.\

{BLOCK:1}
` So they're three or more, huh?@
` I wonder if that all-female group is really carrying out those orgies at school...@
` Does that mean Ohta was part of them?@
` It'd have been helpful if Shinjo observed them a little more closely...\

{BLOCK:2}
` Anyway, even if they're only girls, I'd have a hard time brawling with three of them.@
` I'll try to avoid that scenario as much as I can.@
` I'm glad I was able to gather at least that piece of information.\