{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAADMAAAAA/P/1//T/zf8AzP//q/+r/qsA/av8q/v4+voA+/n/+Pv39/YA89f73f7X+9yh3/7b3/7a/v8AAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:10}

{BLOCK:0}
After thinking for a while, I say resolutely:@
"I'm sorry, but I can't take you with me.@ It'll be late at night, and dangerous."@
{CHARA:r10}
Shinjo puffs out her cheeks a bit and is about to reply something, but instead she cuts herself short and lets out a small sigh.@
"Fuh...@ Alright, you got it.@ I understand your point."\

{BLOCK:1}
"Sorry."@
"Oh, please don't worry!@ I know I was asking for something ridiculous."@
Shinjo says with a sweet smile.@
"If you want to ask me something else, come to the 2nd gym.@ I'll be there training in the club."@
"Yeah, thank you".\c
{CHARA:r13}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
"Anyway, good luck with the investigation, Sherlock junior!"@
She winks.@ That's yet another of her mischievous quirks.@
"Thanks."@
{CHARA:r99}
Shinjo pats my shoulder as a sort of farewell gift and walks away through the hallway.@
As I look at her back, she stops five, maybe six meters away, and turns around to me.\c
{CHARA:r10}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
"But nothing is stopping me from investigating on my own, right?"@
"Wha--?!"@
{CHARA:r16}
I gasp unable to finish my sentence, and Shinjo chuckles as if making fun of me.@
"I'm kidding!@ It was only a lil' joke!"@
"S-Shinjo..."@
"Anyway, bye-bye!"@
{CHARA:r99}
Shinjo then keeps walking away with lively steps.\c
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:03}
\e

{BLOCK:4}
What she just said made my heart skip a beat.@
I hope she's not serious about tagging along...@
I definitely don't dislike her, but she's a very unpredictable girl.@
She makes me feel anxious.\

{BLOCK:5}
But, leaving that aside, I obtained pretty valuable info from Shinjo.@
Now I know...\p\n\e

{BLOCK:6}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. That three or more girls (the shadows) were there.\n\e

{BLOCK:7}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. That the shadows were sighted near the gym.\n\e

{BLOCK:8}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
3. That the ghost craze started two or three weeks ago.\n\e

{BLOCK:9}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
4. The hours where the ghosts usually appear.\n\e