{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAC0AAAAA/P/1//T/0/8A0v//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4+Pr3/fYA//X71/ua/tcH+97+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:11}

{BLOCK:0}
"Do you want to ask me something else?"@
Shinjo asks tilting her head.@
"Hmm, I think this is enough for now..."@
"Well?@ Was I helpful?"@
"Yeah, you helped me quite a lot."@
"I see.@ Good to hear."@
She places her hand in her hip and nods cheerfully.\

{BLOCK:1}
"By the way, Nagase, I have a little proposal..."@
Shinjo stares fixedly at me as she draws close.@
I feel a little nervous.@
"W-What proposal?"@
Shinjo chuckles, lifts her index finger,@
{CHARA:r13}
"Mind if I join the survey?"@
and suggests that flashing a wink.\

{BLOCK:2}
"No, that's a no-go.@ This is not a game."@
Yeah.@ This is a dangerous case that could escalate into a police investigation.@ It'd be unbereable if she tagged along thinking we're playing detective.@
{CHARA:r1D}
"So rude!"@
She pouts and places her hand in her hip.@
"I'm not taking this as a game, y'know?!"@
"Then why do you want to join?"\

{BLOCK:3}
"I told you before that I hate people that make a ruckus around ghosts and supernatural stuff, but if there's somthing I'll never tolerate is people that CAUSE the ruckus!"@
She clenches her fist in front of her chest.@
{CHARA:r10}
"I'm positive these people are having fun spooking everyone with ghosts stories."\

{BLOCK:4}
I think that's pretty far from reality.@ They don't want to cause a fuss about ghosts.@
After all, that might backfire and draw attention from people around the school.@
Their actual goal lies somewhere else: having wild sexual parties without being noticed.\c
{CHARA:r12}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
"That's why I want to yell at them in their face: "STOP RIGHT NOW!""@
Then, Shinjo peeks into my face.@
{CHARA:r11}
"Well?@ Can I join?"@
"But still..."\c
{CHARA:r10}
\e

{BLOCK:6}
However, I feel somewhat grateful that Shinjo wants to join the survey.@
I'd feel reassured with her by my side.@
After all, I'll be alone in this creepy school late at night.@ Creepier even if some weird incident were to happen.@
If someone as bright as a midsummer sun like her is next to me, the mood will naturally become bright too.@
That in itself would be a great advantage, without mentioning I'll able to rely more on her information.@
Perhaps it'd be a good idea to consider herself seriously.\c
{CHARA:r11}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
"C'mon, pretty please!@ I'll do my very best.@ I swear I'll be helpful to you!"@
She begs to join with an awkward smile.@
Hmm, it's hard to turn her down when she asks me like that...\

{BLOCK:8}
Anyway, what will I do?\n\e

{BLOCK:9}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. Let her join the investigation.\n\e

{BLOCK:10}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. Reject her firmly.\n\e