{HEADER:AQAGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAADkAAAAA/P/1//T/x/8Axv//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/Or8qsA8avwq++r7qsA7bi7/vvI/v9/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:19}

{BLOCK:0}
A full, round moon hangs up in the sky.@
Illuminated by faint moonlight, our bodies shine like pale flames.@
At our feet, our shadows are clearly projected under that moonlight.@
I don't know why, but this scene looks very mystic to me.\c
{BGMPLAY:12}
{VISUAL:010000}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
I'm resting against Ruriko's chest.@
She closes her eyes slightly, and completely silent, she hugs my head.@
The calm sound of her breath...@ Her heartbeats...@ The quiet motions of her chest...@ Her body temperature...@ Her sighs...@
The definite presence of Ruriko entices me to a sleep-inducing relief.@
A sense of relief envelops me, like a kid embraced by his mother.#

{BLOCK:2}
"Ruriko..."@
I call her name faintly with my face buried in her soft bosom, and she slowly turns around to look at me.@
"Why me?"@
I ask, but Ruriko's body doesn't show the slightest response.@
"We were in the same class last year, but when we were promoted to somophores, we stopped seeing each other completely.@ No...@ I think you didn't know about me at all even back then."#

{BLOCK:3}
` She's a hard-to-approach bishojo, and on top of that, she's always reading books.@ She's a very quiet girl.@
` If she were a character from an old classical novel, she'd probably be described as a closeted maiden.@
` The idol of the boys of our class.@
` That's why I never talked to her.@

{BLOCK:4}
"The Denpa messages...@ Why did you send them to me?@ Is there a reason why you chose me?"@
I lift my face from her chest.@
That small question bugged me in a corner of my mind.@
Up until now, she paid absolutely no attention to my answers.@
But, we both think that that in itself holds no meaning.#

{BLOCK:5}
However, now...@ Now things are different.@
Little by little, that question grew bigger inside me along with my feelings for her, and it eventually became so big I can't ignore it anymore.@
Why is Ruriko so nice to me?@
Is it because it's ME?@
Or could it be because...?@
I can't stop asking myself those questions.#

{BLOCK:6}
Ruriko cracks her usual languid smile, and after a brief silence, she slowly opens her mouth.@
"Naga..."@
"Huh?"@
"You...@ called for me."@
"Me?"@
I blink two, three times.@
"You called for me every single day.@ "Please save me!", you said."@
"What do you mean...?"#

{BLOCK:7}
Ruriko embraces me strongly.@
"You were crying like a kid.@ "I'm going to disappear!" and such.@ That message became Denpa waves and I received it."@
"Me?@ Disappearing?"@
"You sent me that message every day."@
"......"#

{BLOCK:8}
That I'm about to disappear?@
ME?@
How come?@
That I was crying every day?@
Why would I be so sad...?#

{BLOCK:9}
However, I knew the answer from long ago.@
I know that better that anybody else.#

{BLOCK:10}
My existence was about to disappear from the real world.#

{BLOCK:11}
I had the strange feeling that the same film looped every single day at exactly the same hour.@
A repetitive everyday where nothing ever changes in the picture.@
Eventually, I noticed all the color from this world vanished.#

{BLOCK:12}
In such a world, I was crying all alone.@
I cried like a kid that I was about to disappear, so I looked for someone else to help me.#

{BLOCK:13}
"That's why I thought I'd help you."@
Ruriko's snowy, cold hand gently strokes my back.@
"I'll save you.@ I promise I'll save you, Naga."@
"Ruriko..."@
"So... don't cry anymore, okay?"@
Ruriko says peeking into my face.@
Eyes unfocused like a lake under a moon night.@
The eyes of a person whose spirit broke down.#

{BLOCK:14}
"How strange.@ You always knew everything about me..."@
Just a few hours before we were only classmates that conversated every now and then...@
"My voice reached you, didn't it?"@
Yeah, and your voice reached me too.#

{BLOCK:15}
Ruriko cowering and quivering...@
Her teardrops flowing down her cheeks...@
The light ripples spreading through the puddle...#

{BLOCK:16}
That's Ruriko's inner world.@
The voice of her heart.#

{BLOCK:17}
"You said we were alike.@ I think I know what you meant now."@
Ruriko keeps looking at me, always smiling.@
"Please save me, Ruriko, because I'll save you too..."@
"Yes..."#

{BLOCK:18}
Golden moonlight illuminates both of us.@
We embrace each other like two inanimate objects as we feel the breath of each other.\c
{BGMNEXT:03}
{BGMFOUT}
{BG:360505}
\e