{HEADER:AQAGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEIAAAAA/P/1//T/vv8Avf//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/Or8qsA8avwq++r7qsA7avsq+ur6qsA6avoq+f7nf4//wAA}
{BLOCKLEN:25}

{BLOCK:0}
After opening the emergency exit, Mizuho and another person enter the building.@
It'd be bad if they closed the door and locked themselves inside.@
"Mizuho!"@
I run to chase them while shouting Mizuho's name at the top of my lungs.@
She reacts surprisedly to my voice, and turns around.\c
{CHARA:r21}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"Yuusuke!"@
Mizuho stops in her tracks and covers her mouth with her hand.@
The bandaged man next to her switfly steps in between us.@
Under the yellow moonlight, their appearance becomes clear.@
The bits of face revealed behind all the bandage are unmistakably female.@
In her cheeks are carved scars, which are painful to look at.@
That injuries...@ Don't tell me she is...#

{BLOCK:2}
After approaching her, I confirm my suspicions.@
There's no mistake.@
The bandaged man...@ No, the bandaged girl is...\c
{CHARA:l31}
{BGMPLAY:19}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
Ohta.#

{BLOCK:4}
Kanako Ohta.@
The student council's vice president and my classmate, and Mizuho's irreplaceable best friend.@
Three days ago she harmed herself scratching her cheeks with her own nails, thus causing those painful wounds.@
If Ohta's here, does that mean my uncle's speculation wasn't wrong after all?#

{BLOCK:5}
After she suddenly snapped mid-class, she was transported to a hospital in an ambulance and, supposedly, remained hospitalized up until now.@ How come she's here now?@
Did she escape?@
It doesn't sound too far-fetched.#

{BLOCK:6}
In her diary, Ohta showed a pathological sexual desire, akin to a drug addict craving illicit substances.@
Now that she operates on mere instinct after losing her mind, perhaps it's only natural she'd come here.#

{BLOCK:7}
Ohta's eyes are just like they were three days ago.@
Unfocused and cloudy like a muddy swamp under a moon night.@
The eyes of a person who suffered a mental breakdown.@
The same eyes Ruriko has.#

{BLOCK:8}
With a broad smile on her face, she looks at me with the same awkwardness of a broken machine.@
A chill races up my spine.@
Her gaze is as cold as ice.@
Once I reach both of them, I pass before Ohta to avoid her gaze, and then grab Mizuho's slender shoulders.#

{BLOCK:9}
"Mizuho!"@
{CHARA:r24}
"Y-Yusuke..."@
Mizuho makes the most awkward face I could ever describe, and drops her gaze to the floor.@
"You promised me you wouldn't come!"@
"S-Sorry.@ I-I was so worried about Kanako that...@ Well..."#

{BLOCK:10}
"For starters, why is Ohta with you?"@
{CHARA:r21}
"I went looking for you ready to be scolded, and by chance...@ I mean, literally by chance, I met Kanako who seems to have escaped from the hospital..."@
I give a fleeting glance at Ohta.@
Ohta stares back at us with a wide grin.@
I get goosebumps, and a chill runs down my spine.@
She doesn't look like a living human being.@
Nonsensical thoughts like that cross through my mind.#

{BLOCK:11}
"O-Ohta...@ Did you escape from the hospital?"@
I ask, but she doesn't answer at all.@
{CHARA:r24}
"It's useless to talk to Kanako as she is now.@ She doesn't listen to a word I say, either."@
Mizuho hangs her head with a sad face.@
"Really?"@
With muddy, cloudy eyes, Ohta glares at us as she curls her lips.#

{BLOCK:12}
"It looks like she's not her usual self."@
{CHARA:r2B}
"Perhaps she hasn't still healed?"@
I doubt she'll ever recover again.@
That's what I think, but I decide not to tell her.@
"Where were you two heading to?"@
"It seems Kanako wants to go somewhere.@ That's why I'm accompanying her."@
Mizuho says looking at me with straight eyes.#

{BLOCK:13}
"Fine.@ I'll follow her, so you go home now."@
As soon as I say that, Mizuho opens wide her eyes.@
{CHARA:r26}
"N-No!@ Please take me with you!@ I beg you!"@
"No."@
I decline firmly.@

{BLOCK:14}
"For the umpteenth time, this is a very dangerous case.@ If something serious happens, I won't be able to protect you!"@
"I don't care!"@
"How come?!@ It's your own safety!"@
"But I can't leave Kanako alone!"@
"M-Mizuho..."@
I'm at a loss for words before her overwhelming demands.#

{BLOCK:15}
Her shoulders are quivering, and her eyes are slightly teary.@
She's seriousness incarnate.@
I knew she was a bit obstinate, but I had no idea she was the kind of girl that tries to impose her own beliefs over other people.@
Mizuho looks terrified at her own forcefulness.@
Given Ohta's in the equation, she's so agitated she unable to get a hold of herself.#

{BLOCK:16}
"Please!@ I beg you! PLEASE!@ PLEASE TAKE ME WITH YOU!"@
*Drip* *Drip*@ Tears flow down from her eyes.@
"......"@
I wait for a minute or so, and then let out a small sigh.#

{BLOCK:17}
"Okay, you win."@
{CHARA:r2A}
"Yuu... suke..."@
{CHARA:r23}
Mizuho wipes the tears in the inner part of her glasses.@
"In exchange, I want you to forget about me and escape at the least sign of danger."@
"Yes, I promise."@
{CHARA:r2A}
"Besides..."#

{BLOCK:18}
At that very moment, Mizuho's clear eyes open wide out of the blue.@
{REFCHAR:r26}
"N-No!@ Kanako...!"@
"Mizuho...?"@
"Yuusuke!@ Watch o--!"@
In unison with Mizuho's shout...\c
{BGMSTOP}
\e

{BLOCK:19}
{QUAKE}
{FLASH}
*THUMP*!#

{BLOCK:20}
The instant I feel a heavy impact in the back of my head, my consciousness fades away at an alarming speed...\c
{BG:000011}
\e

{BLOCK:21}
*THUD*!@
I hear something falling to the ground.#

{BLOCK:22}
A-A rock?!@
Yeah, it's indeed a rock...@ And a gigantic one of top of that...#

{BLOCK:23}
Hold up.@ Was I hit in the head with THAT enormous boulder?!@
Shouldn't I be dead?@
Who the hell did it?@
Ohta?!@
Ohta, huh?@ I see.@ Yeah, that's most natural...#

{BLOCK:24}
Accepting the truth in a strange way, I let myself fall into a jet-black darkness.#