{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAC8AAAAA/P/1//T/0f8A0P//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/f4+vZA/f8A+9f71f7XB/vU/v8AAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:12}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:410707}
A clear sky spreads in this comfortable twilight.@
The slightly chill wind strokes our cheeks.@
There's a single tree planted in the lawn spread all over the courtyard, and that's where we stop.\c
{CHARA:r20}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"You want to talk with me about letting me help you or not, don't you?"@
She asks as she peeks into my expression.@
"Um, yeah..."@
{CHARA:r21}
"Please let me join!"@
Seeing I falter as I talk, Mizuho demands to cooperate with a serious face.@
"I want to do something... anything to help Kanako!"\

{BLOCK:2}
Mizuho stares at me with straight eyes.@
She usually looks weak-minded, but she can get very hot-blooded when her emotions well up.@
I'm at a loss for words because I don't know how to answer, but...@
{CHARA:r24}
"Ah, sorry."@
She apologizes and gives a step back.@
Then, she slowly opens her mouth.\

{BLOCK:3}
"I already went to visit Kanako a lot of times."@
Ohta has been admitted in a local hospital since Monday.@
"At first they didn't let me visit her, but yesterday they let me speak to her for a while."@
"How was she?"@
I'm concerned too.@ Not about Ohta, but about the post-traumatic state of a person that suffered a heavy mental breakdown.\

{BLOCK:4}
"Ohta has been sleeping all this time.@ No, in fact, her eyes are open, but she keeps staring at the celing as quiet as if she were sleeping."@
Little by little, Mizuho's voice becomes a sob.@
"No matter how many times I call her name, Kanako never responds.@ Her mom tried to call her too, but it was useless..."@
"I see..."\

{BLOCK:5}
"The doctors told her mom she might stay like that forever."@
{CHARA:r23}
Mizuho rubs both of her eyes as her slenders shoulders tremble.@
I fail to find any appropriate words to soothe her.@
"But maybe... just maybe...@ If I help in tonight's investigation, I could find a hint to open Kanako's heart.@ That's why I... I..."\

{BLOCK:6}
I see.@ Now I have a better grasp of the situation.@
That's the reason why Mizuho wants to join the survey so badly.@
If possible, I'd like to cooperate with her.@
If, as she said, we can find a hint to recover her consciousness, I want to find that by all means possible.\

{BLOCK:7}
That said, bringing her to the investigation is a different matter entirely.@
I might as well just tell everything I see to Mizuho.@ Also, right now she's too eager to help because she can't keep quiet about this.@
What I should keep in mind to make my choice is if Mizuho will be helpful for the investigation or not.\c
{CHARA:r21}
\e

{BLOCK:8}
"Please, Yuusuke!"@
"Wait a minute.@ There's something I want to ask you first.@ Please answer me."@
{CHARA:r20}
"Ah, yes, sure."@
Mizuho takes a breath.@ She looks calmed down now.\

{BLOCK:9}
What I want to ask her is...\n\e

{BLOCK:10}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. About Ohta coming to school late at night.\n\e

{BLOCK:11}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. If she noticed something strange in Ohta before the incident.\n\e