{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABgAAAAA/P/1//T/6P8A5///q/+r/qsA/av8+7r+/wAA}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
Certainly, it wouldn't be wise to come out now.@
I should assess the situation for a while more.@
All the more if the person next to Mizuho is a member of the offender group.@
If I take action now, not only they'll notice me, but I'd be putting Mizuho in danger, and perhaps even Ruriko too.#

{BLOCK:1}
My ultimate goal is to run the survey, not confronting them face to face.@
Of course, if I judge Mizuho's in danger, I'll go rescue her immediately.@
However, that doesn't seem to be the case.@
Anyway, for now, I'll just watch over her.#

{BLOCK:2}
"Fine.@ I won't go."@
I say, and Ruriko slowly lets go of my hand.@
{CHARA:r00}
She's staring at me with an unfocused gaze.@
Why did she stop me?@
Did she analyze the situation calmly?@ Did she think I was being reckless?@ She felt herself in danger?@ Or... is she concerned about me?@
I feel she wouldn't answer those questions if I asked her.#

{BLOCK:3}
{BG:151010}
When I point my gaze to the building, Mizuho and the other person already entered the building.@
I take a look around, and after making sure no shadow is around, I slowly approach the emergency exit.#