{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABkAAAAA/P/1//T/5/8A5v//q//Cu/4A/PvG/vvH/v9/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:1}

{BLOCK:0}
The clock marks 9 P.M.@
There isn't a single member the club left now.@ 20 minutes passed after I made sure the last group of students crossed the door.@
The school building, the gym, the room for each athletics club...@ Each and every light in the rooms is out.@
Today, the school becomes quiet fairly earlier than usual.#