{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABwAAAAA/P/1//T/5P8A4///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+vsPvv7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:6}

{BLOCK:0}
Hold up.@
Shinjo said the club members leave the gym key next to the "leaving notebook" every time they exit.#

{BLOCK:1}
I look around.@
There's a janitor room with small glass windows.@
I open the unlocked door.@
{BG:000311}
After taking a look inside, I find several keys hanging in a wall.@
The leaving notebook is on the desk below.@
I take it and flip the pages.#

{BLOCK:2}
In the last row of the last page is written:@
"March 6, 8:35 P.M, girls volley club, Shinjo".@
It seems the last one who left today was Shinjo.@
I put the notebook back in the desk and take the 2nd gym's key labeled as such.#

{BLOCK:3}
I open the gym door with that key.@
{BG:521103}
The inside is dark.@ Only the moon illuminates faintly from the window.@
Everything is dead silent, and I find nobody around.#

{BLOCK:4}
We enter...@
{BG:270303}
the changing room,
{BG:530303}
the toilet,
{BG:260303}
the equipment room,
{BG:520303}
and the guidance room, but after patrolling thoroughly, we find nothing of interest.#

{BLOCK:5}
It seems nothing weird happened the 2nd gym...#