{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAB4AAAAA/P/1//T/4v8A4f//q/+r/rgAvP7Cv//8+9kD/vvY/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:2}

{BLOCK:0}
Judging by Shinjo's story, they lurk near the gym every night.@
Instead of exploring the school at random, it'd be more efficient to look into the most questionable places.@ I'm more likely to find something that way.\

{BLOCK:1}
They're near the gym.@ The 2nd gym, to be precise, since the volleyball club girls sighted them.@
I'll focus my investigation there since it's the most suspicious area.\