{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACgAAAAA/P/1//T/2P8A1///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0+77+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:12}

{BLOCK:0}
We begin the investigation.@
First of all, the school premises.\c
{BG:290303}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
We move to the front gate.@
Obviously, the door is locked, so I input the code my uncle told me.@
0...@ *Pip*...@ 8...@ *Pip*...@ 2...@ *Pip*...@ 4...@ *Pip*...@
*Ziiim!*@ The electronic lock is released along with the roar of a motor.@
I insert the master key in the hole, then remove it, and the door slowly opens.\c
{BG:440303}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
The school building is eerily silent and filled with cold air.@
As I expected, there's no trace of human presence here.@
I don't think there's anybody here.\c
{BG2:440303}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
We start walking around.@
Warm moonlight lights up the pitch-black darkness.@
I can't make out anything, no matter how closely I look or hear.\c
{BG:050303}
\e

{BLOCK:4}
We enter every room there is, but we don't find anything worth mentioning.\c
{BG:460303}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
The staff room.@
There's no way they're perfoming those strange meetings here...\c
{BG:480303}
\e

{BLOCK:6}
2nd floor, 3rd floor...@
Nothing in sight.\c
{BG:150303}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
We don't find anything in the school building, so we look elsewhere.\c
{BG:110303}
\e

{BLOCK:8}
We exit the main building and patrol near the gym.@
Here's where Shinjo saw those suspicious shadows.#

{BLOCK:9}
The 2nd gym is the newest one and it's used by the volleyball club, known for being one of the strongest teams in the prefecture.@ They always stay up late practicing.@
That said, there's not a soul at these hours.#

{BLOCK:10}
The moonlight projects our shadows clearly on the floor, which allows us to see very far away without any light source.@
Sakura trees line up around the gym.@
For now, we just walk along it.@
We make sure we don't miss any shadow or light source.@ However, we don't find anything.#

{BLOCK:11}
Next we enter the gym.@
The door is locked.@
I insert the master key my uncle gave me.@
However, the key doesn't work.@
Apparently, this key only works inside the school building, which the gym doesn't belong to.@
Our search range narrowed a little, but there's hardly anything we can do about it.@
If the investigation continues until tomorrow, I'll ask for this key to my uncle.#