{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAB8AAAAA/P/1//T/4f8A4P//q/+r/qsA/av8wrz+/PsBwv77w/7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:150303}
It was a strange experience.@
I wonder if it was a sort of sleep paralysis.@
Despite my mind was as sharp as a knife, I lost all freedom in my body.@
Was Ruriko behind it?@
First the electricity rushing in my head, and now this...@ Is Ruriko really able to use denpa waves?@
Was she the one who paralyzed me?#

{BLOCK:1}
We're not in a silly SF movie.@
How come poisonous denpa waves are pouring down from the sky?@
I smile at my own foolishness.@
My body just froze sub-consciously after being treated so coldly by Ruriko.@
Without a doubt, I hesitated to chase Ruriko back then.@
Her teardrops froze my body.#

{BLOCK:2}
As I think about that, it finally becomes time to run the survey.#

{BLOCK:3}
I'm worried about Ruriko, but despite I look everywhere, I can't find her.@
My plan to bring her along flopped brilliantly.@
Appartenly Ruriko thinks I was making fun of denpa waves.@
That wasn't my intention...@
Perhaps I took it too far...#