{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABwAAAAA/P/1//T/5P8A4///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+vsP1v7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:6}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:130404}
As I thought, Mizuho was in the S.C's room.@
"Ah!"@
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:06}
{CHARA:r22}
When I call out to her, a big smile appears on her face and she comes running over to me like a puppy.@
"Glad you're here, Yuusuke."@
"I promised I'd come, didn't I?"@
"Yes, thank you."@
She nods.@
Every gesture she does gives me the impression of an obedient, docile girl.\

{BLOCK:1}
"Thank you very much for coming all the way here."@
She says apologetically.@
"It was no big deal, really..."@
I take a wide look at the room.@
There are some members of the S.C. talking together.@ Crazy to think that, until last week, Ohta was working along with them as the beloved vicepresident...@

{BLOCK:2}
"Are you guys in a meeting?"@
{CHARA:r20}
"Oh, no, we aren't, but..."@
Mizuho looks at me with upturned eyes and a somewhat obscure smile in her face.@
"Okay then, we'll collect 1500 yen each one for the flowers, right, Mizuho?"@
One of the female students tells to Mizuho.@
"Y-Yes, thank you."@
She answers.@

{BLOCK:3}
"Flowers?@ Are you going to visit Ohta?"@
"Yes.@ I thought about sending flowers to her."@
Mizuho was friends with Ohta since childhood, so she probably wants to send flowers in representation of the S.C. since she's currently hospitalized.\

{BLOCK:4}
"By the way, I want to talk with you about something.@ Got a minute?"@
I tell her, pointing my gaze towards the other students in the room.@
I'd be awkward to discuss THAT topic here.@
Fortunately, Mizuho grasps my intention without delay.@
"Yes.@ Please excuse me, but I have a little business with Yuu--... Nagase."@
With those parting words, she leaves the staff room and closes the door.\c
{BG:490404}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
"Let's talk right there in the courtyard."@
"Yes."@
I take Mizuho with me and leave for the courtyard.\