{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACQAAAAA/P/1//T/3P8A2///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9vsPuf7/AAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:10}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:110303}
I'm before the 2nd gym.#

{BLOCK:1}
I didn't find a single clue yet.@
Perhaps I've been patrolling the wrong places?@
That said, as long as the culprits doesn't show themselves, we don't have choice but to walk around and investigate straightforwardly.#
Shall we go for an exhaustive search?#

{BLOCK:2}
At that moment...@
{BGMSTOP}
"!"@
Although they disappared from my field of sight immediately, I spotted human shadows illuminated by the moonlight far away.#

{BLOCK:3}
There were two persons.@
Perhaps they're who I was looking for.@
They cross the back of the gym and disappear in the building.@
I chase them back immediately.@
But, I go step by step to avoid being noticed.#

{BLOCK:4}
{BGMPLAY:05}
I wasn't wrong.@
There's two human-like shadows there.@
I chase them immediately.@
It seems they're trying to enter the building from the emergency exit in the east stairs.@
After they open the door with the key, they come into view under the moonlight.#

{BLOCK:5}
At first I thought one of them was hiding their face, and thus their gender, behind a mask.@
However, looking at them closely, I notice it isn't a mask, but a piece of white fabric.@
It's white bandages.@
He (or she) has his face covered with white bandages, like a mummy in a horror movie.#

{BLOCK:6}
Then, when the other person becomes visible...@
"!"@
I let out an unintentional gasp.@
I know that face.@
Slightly curly, chestnut-color hair...@ Big glasses...@ A face a bit childish...@
It's the S.C's secretary, Mizuho Aihara.#

{BLOCK:7}
Mizuho...@
Yeah, no doubt it's her.#

{BLOCK:8}
I can't believe she ACTUALLY came...@
I kinda expected it, but I regret not stopping her before.@
Who's the person next to her?@ A friend she brought along?@
That's fine, but, what if she's taking active part in the meetings?@
Alcohol.@ Drugs.@ Sex.@ Rape...@
Those nouns my uncle mentioned flash through my mind and froze my spine.#

{BLOCK:9}
Mizuho and the other person are about to enter the building.@
I gotta save her!\c
{BG:150202}
\e