{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACkAAAAA/P/1//T/1/8A1v//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+vgA+vr9+f/4+9cA+83+1/vO/v9/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:8}

{BLOCK:0}
In the red sunset sky, a sun akin to a red-hot furnace projects our shadows sharply on the concrete floor.@
Both of our shadows cast by low-angled sunrays extend a long way from our feet, joining at the end and overlapping each other.#

{BLOCK:1}
This red sky reminds me of amber-hot metal melting in a furnace, fireworks, or sparklers.@
It's a dull, beautiful red.@
A color befitting of Ruriko, who possess both the innocence of a young maiden and the insanity of a lunatic.

{BLOCK:2}
Ruriko leans against the fence while looking at me.@
Holding down her hair with a hand, she narrows her eyes slowly and then cracks a gentle smile.@
"You finally came."@
I stop on my tracks.@
"Me?"@
"Yeah.@ I was calling you all this time."@
A world dyed red.@
Her hair, skin, uniform, eyes, nose, mouth, nails...@
All of it colored with a charming, muddy crimson hue.#

{BLOCK:3}
"You called me?"@
"Yep.@ I was telling you to hurry up."@
She says as the pure smile of a childish lady appears on her face.@
"Did they reach you?"@
"Huh?@ What?"@
"The denpa waves."@
"Denpa...?@ O-Oh, you mean those signals..."@
I recall the conversation I had with her earlier today.#

{BLOCK:4}
"I sent you a message with my denpa waves.@ Have you received them?"@
"A message...?"@
Ruriko never stops smiling.@
I have no idea if she's serious or she's just pulling my leg.#

{BLOCK:5}
My answer is...\n\e

{BLOCK:6}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. Yeah, you guided me here.\n\e

{BLOCK:7}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. No, I didn't receive anything.