{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACgAAAAA/P/1//T/2P8A1///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0+9f+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:12}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:060303}
After leaving Shinjo behind, I drop by 2-A classroom.@
As we agreed, I'm going to meet Mizuho.@
I grab a random student and ask them if Mizuho's in there.@
However, they tell me she isn't.@
Then, I remember what she told me before.\

{BLOCK:1}
"Whenever I'm not in the classroom, I stay at the student council."\

{BLOCK:2}
The student council, huh?@ Alright, I'm gonna head there.\c
{BG:431010}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
Despite we know where the student council is inside the school, 90% of us students have never done so much as setting foot in it.@
Aside from school festivals, the student council and their members are like a faint, elusive entity.@
Regular students like us have no idea about half of what they do inside there.\

{BLOCK:4}
As long as they're given a certain degree of freedom, common students never complain.@
It's merely their school life, so as long as someone takes care of their problems, they're fine.@ Instead of bothering themselves with the most tedious tasks, they choose the easy way.@
The same applies to the national politics of the country.@
That's why regular students have no concern regarding the student council.\c
{BG:490303}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
At the endpoint of the row of cultural clubs lined up one next to each other, the nameplate labeled "Student council" stands out quietly.@
Club presidents often come and go, but aside from that, the room is always closed.\

{BLOCK:6}
I approach the door and try to knock the door, but immediately lift my hand back.@
*Trac*@
The very instant I'm about to knock, the door opens first and hits my right hand.\c
{CHARA:r40}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
"Oh, sorry, did I hurt you?"@
A tall, young man shows his face from inside.@ I've never seen him before.@
If I recall correctly, he was the student council president the previous semester.@
His name is Tsukishima.@
Yeah, he's... Ruriko's big brother.@
"N-No, it's nothing."\

{BLOCK:8}
"Alright, please take care of the rest."@
{CHARA:r99}
Tsukishima tells to someone inside the room, and after apologizing again he walks away along the hallway.@
Then, a certain thought flashes through my mind.@
What if I stop him and ask him about Ruriko...?\

{BLOCK:9}
"Did something happen to your sister?"@
I wonder how would he reply to that...\

{BLOCK:10}
Will he be bothered by such a sudden question?@
Will he consider it a rude question and get angry?@
Or will he tell me the whole story behind her?\

{BLOCK:11}
However, when I turn my gaze to him once more, he's nowhere to be seen.\