{HEADER:AQAGAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAADcAAAAA/P/1//T/yf8AyP//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0q/P4+vIA/fH/8PvX+7sB/tf7vP7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:16}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:110303}
We're before the 2nd gym.#

{BLOCK:1}
We didn't find a single clue yet.@
Perhaps we're patrolling the wrong places?@
That said, as long as the culprits doesn't show themselves, we don't have choice but to walk around and investigate straightforwardly.#

{BLOCK:2}
Shall we go for an exhaustive search?@
{CHARA:r02}
As I think about that, I casually look at Ruriko's face.@
She's wearing a complex expression as she stares fixedly at the building.#

{BLOCK:3}
"What are you looking at, Ruriko?"@
{CHARA:r00}
I ask her, and she looks back at me.@
"What's wrong?"@
{CHARA:r02}
She slowly reaches her right arm horizontally, and points to the building.@
"There's people in that direction."@
She says with an expressionless, emotionless face.#

{BLOCK:4}
"People?!"@
I turn my gaze to where she pointed.@
And there...@
{BGMSTOP}
"!"@
Yeah, they're there!@
They immediately vanished from our field of sight, but they WERE there.@
Two persons.@
"Let's go!"\c
{REFCHAR:r99}
{BGMPLAY:05}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
Both shadows crossed the back of the gym and disappeared into the building.@
We run and chase them immediately.@
But, we're careful enough not to being noticed...#

{BLOCK:6}
We reach them in no time.@
It looks like the shadows want to enter the building from the emergency exit by the east stairs.@
When they open the door with the key, they're illuminated by the moonlight and their figures are clearly seen.#

{BLOCK:7}
At first I thought one of them was hiding their face, and thus their gender, behind a mask.@
However, looking at them closely, I notice it isn't a mask, but a piece of white fabric.@
It's white bandages.@
He (or she) has his face covered with white bandages, like a mummy from a horror movie.#

{BLOCK:8}
Then I see the other one under the moonlight.@
"!"@
I gasp unintentionally.@
I know that face.@
Slightly curly, chestnut-color hair...@ Big glasses...@ A face a bit childish...@
She's the S.C's secretary, Mizuho Aihara.#

{BLOCK:9}
Mizuho...@
I have no doubt it's her.#

{BLOCK:10}
I can't believe she came.@
I kinda expected it, but I regret not stopping her before.@
Who is the person next to her?@ A friend that came along?@
That's fine, but if she were a member of the meetings...@
Alcohol.@ Drugs.@ Sex.@ Rape...@
Those nouns my uncle mentioned flash through my mind, and make my spine chill.#

{BLOCK:11}
"Mizu--...!"@
I run over to Mizuho, but Ruriko's cold hand grabs mine.@
{CHARA:r01}
"Don't go."@
When I turn around, Ruriko's looking fixedly at me.@
"Now it's not the time."@
Ruriko doesn't let go of my hand.@
B-But...#

{BLOCK:12}
I turn my gaze to the emergency exit.@
Mizuho and the other person are about to enter the building.#

{BLOCK:13}
What should I do?\n\e

{BLOCK:14}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. I must stop Mizuho\n\e

{BLOCK:15}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. I'm worried about Mizuho, but for now I'll watch from afar.\n\e