{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABgAAAAA/P/1//T/6P8A5///q/+r/qsA/av8+7n+/wAA}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
Why did she stop me?@
Did she analyze the situation calmly?@ Did she think I was being reckless?@ She felt herself in danger?@ Or... is she concerned about me?@
I feel she wouldn't answer those questions if I asked her.#

{BLOCK:1}
"There's a girl I know there.@ I want to talk with her."@
I say, and Ruriko slowly lets go of my hand.@
However, she keeps staring at me with a slightly troubled expression.#

{BLOCK:2}
"The most logical course of action now would be taling them, but I can't let that girl be exposed to danger."@
Ruriko keeps silent without answering anything.@
"Stay hidden here, Ruriko.@ If you see yourself in danger, forget about me and run.@ Got it?"#

{BLOCK:3}
With those parting words, I left Ruriko behind as she keeps staring fixedly (and silently) at me.\c
{BG:150202}
\e