{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACwAAAAA/P/1//T/1P8A0///q/+r/v4A/P+r/f78/qsA/Kv7q/qr+asA+Kv3q/ar9fsPy/7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:11}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:10}
Inside a pitch-black darkness, I hear someone crying.@
*Sob*@ *Sob*@
Their weeping reaches my ears.#

{BLOCK:1}
{PCMLOAD:17}
Is it a kid?@
No, it isn't.@
It's a young girl.#

{BLOCK:2}
*Plop*@
A drop?@ Yeah, that was a drop.@
A teardrop falling to the ground.@
The drops fall slowly to the water's surface, forming gentle ripples of light.#

{BLOCK:3}
Illuminated by the light of the ripples, the figure of a girl cowering comes into view.@
{PCMWAIT}
{PCMFOUT}
{BGMPLAY:10}
{VISUAL:259912}
That girl is...@ Ruriko.#

{BLOCK:4}
Ruriko...@
Why are you crying?@
What are you so sad about?@
However, my voice doesn't reach her.#

{BLOCK:5}
Another bright ripple spreads out.@
Its light lits up the darkness, and Ruriko's figure appears once again.@
She wears a sailor uniform with ragged sleeves.@ Her hair is messy, and her face is covered in tears.@
Dripping tears...@
that flow down her face as she gets defiled.#

{BLOCK:6}
"I'm sorry, Ruriko."@
I hear that voice coming from beyond the darkness.@
It's the gentle voice of a man.@
"I'm sorry, Ruriko."@
He repeats.@
However, Ruriko keeps crying crouching on the floor.#

{BLOCK:7}
"I love you so much, Ruriko, so why...?@ Why...?"@
Streaming across her cheeks before dropping to the floor, Ruriko's tears form flashing ripples on the puddle below her.@
"Is it really wrong?@ Is it taboo to fall in love with someone and pursue that love to the very end?"@
His voice is pure, innocent, unpolluted.@
A voice that envelops Ruriko tenderly.#

{BLOCK:8}
However, her teardrops keep projecting endless light ripples.@
"I love you, Ruriko.@ I love you, Ruriko."@
Her shoulders tremble along with her weeping.@
"I love you, Ruriko.@ I love you, Ruriko.@ I love you, Ruriko.@ I love you, Ruriko..."@
His voice repeats those words again and again, as is chanting a spell.#

{BLOCK:9}
"I LOVE YOU, RURIKO. I LOVE YOU, RURIKO. I LOVE YOU, RURIKO I LOVE YOU RURIKOILOVEYOURURIKOILOVEYOURURI..."#

{BLOCK:10}
Just like a broken machine, he keeps repeating the same words endlessly...\c
{BG:000611}
\e