{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAC8AAAAA/P/1//T/0f8A0P//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0wrj+/PsB0P77mf7/AAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:12}

{BLOCK:0}
I understand very well how she feels about Ohta.@
She suffered a mental breakdown.@
She never responds no matter how much they talk with her, just like a human vegetable.@
If there's no hope of recovery for her, she might as well be functionally dead.@
Both her guilt for not being able to prevent this incident and her wish to return her best friend to normal are urging Mizuho to join the survey.#

{BLOCK:1}
Perplexed by the sudden incident, she's confused about what to do.@ Even if it's only temporary, Mizuho's beyond herself right now.@
If a culprit for this incident exists, and if she confronts them face to face, how would she react?@
I can only imagine the worst case scenario.#

{BLOCK:2}
At the very least, she's not in a good condition to face this investigation.@
That's what I feel, so I tell her directly:@
"Yeah, I definitely can't take you with me."#

{BLOCK:3}
After hearing those words, Mizuho's face becomes pale of a sudden.@
{CHARA:r21}
"Yuusuke!@ U-Umm..."@
Unable to muster the words she wants to say, she draws closer to me.@
{CHARA:r26}
"P-Please.@ I... I..."#

{BLOCK:4}
"No."@
"Why?!"@
"You're too emotional about Ohta right now."@
{CHARA:r29}
"That's not true!@ I..."@
Despite she denies it, she herself notices she's extremely worked up just like I said, and cut herself short hanging her head in shame.\c
{CHARA:r24}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
"I'll inform you about everything I find in the investigation, without sparing any detail.@ Also, I won't miss any hint that can be useful to open Ohta's heart.@ I can promise you that."@
"......"@
"Besides, it's not like the investigation will be only for tonight.@ If we have to keep patrolling for the next days, I'd like you to cooperate then."#

{BLOCK:6}
Mizuho gulps slowly the words that were about to leave her throat, and finally drops her shoulders as if she gave up.@
"Please understand."@
"......"@
*Nod*@
She nods with a docile expression.\c
{CHARA:r21}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
"Will you really keep that promise?"@
"Absolutely."@
"No matter how small of a detail, please tell me anything you find.@ Perhaps something among that is the key to return Kanako's heart to normal."@
"Yes, I will."@
{CHARA:r22}
"Okay."@
Mizuho smiles sweetly and nods firmly once again.\c
{CHARA:r20}
\e

{BLOCK:8}
"Um, sorry, Yuusuke.@ I did nothing but bother you..."@
"No, I went to ask you first.@ Thanks to you, I obtained a lot of valuable data.@ I appreciate it."@
"N-No, I should be thanking you."@
Mizuho shakes her head and then drops it.@
Then, she says this looking at me upwards:@
{CHARA:r22}
"Anyway, I'll head back to the S.C's room now.@ Good luck with the investigation.@ Please give it your best for me too...@ No, for Kanako."#

{BLOCK:9}
"Okay."@
I give a strong nod.@
{CHARA:r99}
Mizuho narrows her eyes smiling sweetly, and after a deep bow she takes her leave.#

{BLOCK:10}
Honestly, I'm surprised she gave up so easily.@
Mizuho's so single-minded she sometimes shows an obstinate side of hers.@
I thought that, even if I rejected her, she wouldn't accept it without a hitch.@ However, she obediently backed down.@ It's a bit disappointing.@
Wait...@ She didn't feign acceptance knowing well I'd never change my mind... right?#

{BLOCK:11}
Holding a  of anxiety in my heart, I watch her slender back as she leaves.@
When she exits the courtyard, Mizuho looks back at me once more and does a little farewell gesture.@
I answer her waving a hand.#