{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABwAAAAA/P/1//T/5P8A4///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+vsPhv7/AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:6}

{BLOCK:0}
For example, I won't tell her what I'm seeing.@
Well, from here I can see...#

{BLOCK:1}
"!"#

{BLOCK:2}
I realize something.@
I can see the whole school from here.@
I could tell immediately if someone entered from the back door or the front door.#

{BLOCK:3}
I should just watch over from here.@
There's no better place to stand watch than here.@
Wait, does that mean the girl from before was waiting for someone to come to school?@
It's totally possible.#

{BLOCK:4}
"Did you find something, Yuusuke?@ A-Answer me..."@
After hearing Saori's faint voice, I remember my original goal.@
"Ah, sorry.@ There's nothing here."\c
{BG:330303}
\e

{BLOCK:5}
I go back, and Saori clings to my arm once again.@
{CHARA:r14}
"Can we please get away from here?@ I-I'm getting bad vibes from this place..."@
Her voice is feeble.@
Everybody has stuff that they just can't deal with.@
If I hadn't brought up the topic of ghosts back there, maybe she'd have tagged along being her usual bright self.@
"Yeah, you're right.@ Let's do that."@
I'll be careful not to mention anything about ghosts ever again.\c
{CHARA:r99}
\e