{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACsAAAAA/P/1//T/1f8A1P//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+fj6+P33//YA+9f7af7X+2of/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:10}

{BLOCK:0}
{BG:440303}
"Aside from the S.C's room and her classroom, do you know where Ohta could have headed?"@
{CHARA:c20}
"Huh?@ Another place?"@
"Somewhere were you two used to go together."@
{CHARA:c24}
Mizuho hangs her head and ponders about it a little.@
And then, she gives a short answer.@
{CHARA:c20}
"The rooftop."#

{BLOCK:1}
"The rooftop?"@
{CHARA:c22}
"Yes.@ We used to have lunch in the rooftop together every break."@
"Alright, let's go see if she's there."@
"Okay."\c
{BG:480303}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
We both move to the stairs that lead to the rooftop.#

{BLOCK:3}
Casting her gaze to the floor, Mizuho has been thinking about something all the way from the classroom.@
Was it too big of a shock for her?@
Perhaps I should have summarized more my explanation of the case and not tell her absolutely every detail.@
I climb the stairs slowly trying to match my pace to hers and not separating too much from her.#

{BLOCK:4}
Mizuho is the type of person that tends to jump to conclusions, and the more she worries about something, the more seriously she thinks about it.@
Maybe I should talk with her about whatever to distract her from said thoughts.@
Keeping silence for so long in this dark school feels creepy to me.@
Halfway in the stairs that connect the second and third floor, I suddenly come to a halt and call out to Mizuho.#

{BLOCK:5}
"Mizuho..."@
Mizuho lifts her face abruptly.@
"Y-Yes...?"\c
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BG:001011}
\e

{BLOCK:6}
At that very instant, Mizuho slips on the stairs and stumbles.@
"Ah!"@
She loses balance and is about to fall on her back.@
"Watch out!"\c
{BG:481110}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
Right away I reach out my arm to catch her.#

{BLOCK:8}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. Grab her hand.\n\e

{BLOCK:9}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. Grab her hips.\n\e