{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABYAAAAA/P/1//T/6v8A6f//q/+r/qsD/fuJ/v8AAAAA}
{BLOCKLEN:3}

{BLOCK:0}
"Are you scared, Saori?"@
I touch her hand as she helds my arm, and ask her that in a whisper.@
"S-Scared?@ O-Of course not!"@
Out of the blue, Saori separates from me and takes a gutsy stance with a slightly stiff smile.@
She looks like she's forcing herself to fight.@
"G-Ghosts and that stuff...@ are nothing but nonsense..."@
Saori whispers as she hangs her head.@
She's actually scared out of her wits...#

{BLOCK:1}
I think I have a better grasp now of Saori's fear of ghosts.@
It's true that part of the reason is the bad experiences she went through in middle school, but actually, her fear is more instinctual than acquired.#
That explains her prejudice against people who enjoy paranormal stories.@
"Ain't no way ghosts exist."@
She mutters the same thing to herself.@
I find that side of hers to be very adorable.#

{BLOCK:2}
However, this is no time to ponder about that.@
"Let's go investigate."@
I step into the rooftop.@
"Ah..."@
Saori lets out a small gasp, and awkwardly rushes over to me before grabbing tight my arm once again.\c
{BG:330202}
\e