{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACAAAAAA/P/1//T/4P8A3///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4+4b+/wAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:8}

{BLOCK:0}
{CHABG:r00310505}
"Here's where I collect denpa waves every day."#

{BLOCK:1}
Suddenly, I recall Ruriko's words.@
At noon today, after separating from my uncle in the rooftop, I met Ruriko, one of my classmates from last year.@
I haven't seen her for a whole year, but for some reason, she changed 180 degrees from the person I used to know.@
Her high-minded aura dilluted, and now she's like an immaculate, yet mentally immature doll with a mysterious charm around her.#

{BLOCK:2}
In such a state, she told me a couple of strange words.@
Antenna...@
Electric particles...@
Denpa waves...#

{BLOCK:3}
"You have great potential to use the power of denpa waves."\c
{BG:360505}
\e

{BLOCK:4}
Now that I remember, she said I have talent to handle those whatchamacallit waves.@
I still have no idea what she's talking about, but I don't think she was just pulling my leg.@
I recall the pinky promise I exchanged with her.@
My fingertip feels hot...#

{BLOCK:5}
That girl in uniform I saw before reminded me a bit of Ruriko.@
I feel that Ruriko herself could have melted with the rooftop and its nightly mood.@
No, I'm starting to think that human-like silhouette I saw from the hallway was actually Ruriko.@

{BLOCK:6}
"Did you find something, Yuusuke?@ A-Answer me..."@
After hearing Saori's faint voice, I remember my original goal.@
"Ah, sorry.@ There's nothing here."\c
{BG:330303}
\e

{BLOCK:7}
I go back, and Saori clings to my arm once again.@
{CHARA:r14}
"Can we please get away from here?@ I-I'm getting bad vibes from this place..."@
Her voice is feeble.@
Everybody has stuff that they just can't deal with.@
If I hadn't brought up the topic of ghosts back there, maybe she'd have tagged along being her usual bright self.@
"Yeah, you're right.@ Let's do that."@
I'll be careful not to mention anything about ghosts ever again.\c
{CHARA:r99}
\e