{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAC8AAAAA/P/1//T/0f8A0P//q/+r/qsA/av8gfODgu0Awf/+/Ps8/sEh//1v//3B//xv/x/8/wAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:21}
Just as planned, this is the ending.@
We lost our fights against the dimensional aliens.#

{BLOCK:1}
You must not take them lightly.@
In all likelihood, the next alien attack will obliterate us from the world.@
This is your chance to select "Return to last choice" and redo everything.@
However, if you have never seen this ending before, you might as well turn the page.@
A genuinely boring ending awaits you there.#

{BLOCK:2}
Come on, the next one is the final page.@
This is your LAST chance to turn back.#

{BLOCK:3}
{QUAKE}
{FLASH}
*BAM!*@
At that instant, I'm attacked by an enemy alien, and my consciousness fades away.@
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BG:000611}
Before me, freezing darkness spreads everywhere.@
Yeah, I'm...@ dead.@
And as they anticipated, the ending was ridiculously boring...#