{HEADER:AQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABgAAAAA/P/1//T/6P8A5///q/+r/qsA/av8+2T+/wAA}
{BLOCKLEN:4}

{BLOCK:0}
"B-But...@ Umm...@ Some boys like them small..."@
Mizuho's stares at me with her face bright red.@
"I think that size suits you best."@
I add that nonsensical comments as a follow-up.@
{CHARA:c2B}
"D-Do you mean I'm childish?"@
"N-No, that's not what I said..."\c
{CHARA:c24}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"M-My friends use to say I'm childish, even about my height..."@
Mizuho begins to talk in a low voice.@
"Well, it's true that you're growing at a slower pace than everyone, but you're not SO flat-chested that your breasts are unnoticeable when you touch them..."@
I say, and she drops her gaze again.@
Perhaps she's really THIS self-conscious about this topic.\c
{CHARA:c28}
\e

{BLOCK:2}
"N-No, perhaps "unnoticeable" isn't the right word...@ I mean, you breasts are small, but adorable..."@
{CHARA:c2B}
"......"@
Mizuho's eyes dampen little by little.@
This is not working!@
My follow-ups should be more tactful!#

{BLOCK:3}
"I-I, for one, love flat chests like yours!"@
{CHARA:c20}
Mizuho looks at me astonished.@
... OH, CRAP!@
What the hell did I just say?!@
The more I say, the weirder the conversation gets...#