{HEADER:AQAFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACgAAAAA/P/1//T/2P8A1///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4q/er9qsA9av0+3n+/wAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA=}
{BLOCKLEN:12}

{BLOCK:0}
I can't help but think that those "denpa waves" have some deep connection to this case.@
First those girls from the student council and Ohta, and now Saori...@ I think that kind of breakdown is anything but normal.\c
{CHABG:r00310505}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"You can receive Denpa waves, can't you, Nagase?"#

{BLOCK:2}
I recall Ruriko's words from today's afternoon.@
Now that I remember, she mentioned those "Denpa waves".\c
{BG:270505}
\e

{BLOCK:3}
Antenna...@
Electric particles...@
Denpa waves...#

{BLOCK:4}
When I met with her in the rooftop, a sort of electric current ran through my head.@
Back then I thought it was only a physical illusion, but perhaps it wasn't only that.@
That strange electric current from before was exactly like that, but more powerful.#

{BLOCK:5}
Wasn't that current those "Denpa waves" she mentioned?!#

{BLOCK:6}
If that's the case, is Ruriko related to this incident as I suspected at first?@
My conjecture that the person in the rooftop was Ruriko grows stronger.#

{BLOCK:7}
Ohta, the S.C's vice president...@
The other girls from the S.C...@
Takuya Tsukishima, the former president...@
And last but not least, Ruriko Tsukishima.#

{BLOCK:8}
... Huh?@
"Tsukishima"?!@
Yeah, they share the same surname!#

{BLOCK:9}
I'm astonished at my own stupidity.@
How could I forget something so important?!@
Ruriko and Takuya Tsukishima are siblings.#

{BLOCK:10}
Since she was my classmate last year, I saw them going home together a lot of times.@
I recall they got along very well.@
They're indeed siblings, no doubt about it.@
Given such relationship, it's no wonder they share the same oddities.@ In fact, it's the most natural thing to happen.@

{BLOCK:11}
Denpa waves, huh?@
What exactly are they, and why are both siblings so obsessed with them?#