{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACEAAAAA/P/1//T/3/8A3v//q/+r/vgA+v39/P/7+9cA+5H+1/uQ/v9/AAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:5}

{BLOCK:0}
Shinjo must be in the gym, so it'd be faster to go see her than wait for her.@
I then proceed to enter the 2nd gym in order to look for her.#

{BLOCK:1}
Aside from the lights of the door, all the other lamps are turned off.@
The glazed entry door is unlocked, so I enter without trouble.@
{BG:520404}
I open the double leaf door to the arena.@
Moonlight filters through the windows and illuminates faintly the dim inside.@
There's no presence of people here.@
I wonder where Shinjo is...#

{BLOCK:2}
Well, what will I do now?\n\e

{BLOCK:3}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
1. Look for Shinjo everywhere.\n\e

{BLOCK:4}
{XPOS:6}
{SPEED:0}
2. Return to our meeting place.\n\e