{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACAAAAAA/P/1//T/4P8A3///q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsA+av4+1P+/wAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:8}

{BLOCK:0}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMNEXT:23}
{BG:501010}
Perhaps the music box got broken, but its sound stopped, and once again silence falls over the place.@
I wipe the blood off my nose, and walk once more towards Mizuho.@
{CHARA:c32}
Ohta stands between us as if blocking my way.@
Mizuho is right behind her.\c
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
{BGMPLAY:01}
\e

{BLOCK:1}
"Move."@
I say, and put myself on guard.#

{BLOCK:2}
Nothing I tell her will have any effect.@
I knew that way before this.@
But, I don't care if it's useless.@
I just don't want to run away anymore.@
I'm sick of escaping from everything just because it's scary or painful.#

{BLOCK:3}
"Didn't you hear me?@ Move."@
I repeat.@
Ohta looks at me with the eyes of an automaton.@
I ignore her and walk past her.#

{BLOCK:4}
*WHAM!*@
{QUAKE}
{BG:080505}
I take a ridiculously powerful thrust that goes from my solar plexus to my back.@
When I look down, I see Ohta's left fist piercing my stomach.@
I feel something acid welling up in my throat, and then vomit.@
Messy puke stains Ohta's arm.#

{BLOCK:5}
*TWACK!*@
{QUAKE}
Next thing I know, I feel an impact in the back of my head.@
Ohta hit me from behind.@
I feel the world gets shaky, and my field of sights becomes pitch-black.#

{BLOCK:6}
"Yuu... suke..."@
Just before my consciousness leaves this realm, I hear Mizuho's anguished voice.#

{BLOCK:7}
And finally, I faint.\c
{BG:000007}
{BGMFOUT}
{BGMWAIT}
\e