{HEADER:AQAEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAB4AAAAA/P/1//T/4v8A4f//q/+r/qsA/av8q/ur+qsD+fuJ/v8AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA==}
{BLOCKLEN:7}

{BLOCK:0}
"G-Ghosts?@ T-That's so ridiculous..."@
Saori mutters casting her eyes down.@
She looks kind of pale.#

{BLOCK:1}
I think I have a better grasp of Saori's fear of ghosts now.@
It's true that part of the reason is the bad experiences she went through in middle school, but actually, her fear is more instinctual than acquired.#
That explains her prejudice against people who enjoy paranormal stories.@
"Ain't no way ghosts exist."@
She mutters to herself repeatedly.@

{BLOCK:2}
"Don't worry.@ I'm here to protect you."@
I say something unbelievable of me.@
This is weird...@
I'm not the kind of guy that usually says things like these.#

{BLOCK:3}
A coward that runs from anything and everything, that hates the idea of hurting himself and never tries to form connections with other people.@
Hates being burdened with responsibility and absolutely loathes when others ask him for help.@
That's who I am, but now, a certain sense of duty has sprouted inside me.@
That is, protecting Saori at all costs.@
I have to take responsibility for bringing her to this investigation.#

{BLOCK:4}
But...@ it's still strange.@
When I'm with her, the person I was until just yesterday looks to me like a remote, blurry phantom.@
Perhaps Saori's natural brightness outshines my previous, inmaterial self.@
In her presence, my dark side that hates society with a passion, without ever expressing himself or taking action, sleeps and never wakes up.#

{BLOCK:5}
"We're not here to investigate paranormal phenomena, and even if we eventually find the "ghosts", they'll be nothing more than late-night pranksters."@
Saori lifts her worried face and stares at me fixedly.@
"You want to find them and give them a piece of your mind, don't you?"@
Sobbing and looking scared doesn't fit Saori at all.@
Her charm lies in her sunny, bright smile.@
"Yeah."@
Saori nods slowly.#

{BLOCK:6}
If she's so afraid, shouldn't we call it quits for now?@
No, our targets won't wait for us.@
I don't have time to lose withdrawing.@
"If you're okay, let's go."@
Holding Saori's trembling hand, I step into the rooftop.\c
{BG:330202}
\e